<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on ICT 302 Fall 24</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on ICT 302 Fall 24</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 23:30:52 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CMS_Ilunga_victoire</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_ilunga_victoire3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 23:30:52 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_ilunga_victoire3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;definition&#34;&gt;Definition&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content (Baker,2016).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;in-my-own-words&#34;&gt;In my own words&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Content management is the system behind organizing and managing information, like text, images, or videos, that you see on websites. Instead of manually coding or handling files, a &lt;strong&gt;Content Management System (CMS)&lt;/strong&gt; does the work of keeping everything organized and ready for use.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;example&#34;&gt;Example&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;one example for contant management is &lt;strong&gt;Youtube&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/&#34;&gt;youtube&lt;/a&gt;.Creators can upload, organize, and categorize videos into playlists or channels, just like how CMS platforms manage different types of content. Creators can also manage monetization options giving them control over how their content generates revenue.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_kapanga_rael</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_kapanga_rael/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 14:31:20 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_kapanga_rael/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-is-content-aggregation&#34;&gt;what is content aggregation&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;content aggregation is “An intentional grouping of content for the purposes of organization or presentation” Barker, D. (2016).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;explanation-of-content-aggregation-in-my-own-words&#34;&gt;Explanation of Content Aggregation in My Own Words&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;content aggregation involves gathering relevant articles, videos, and other media from various websites and platforms, then presenting them together so users can find and consume information more easily.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;real-life-example-of-content-aggregation&#34;&gt;Real-Life Example of Content Aggregation&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One source of content that I regularly consume is &lt;a href=&#34;https://feedly.com&#34;&gt;Feedly&lt;/a&gt;. Feedly is a content aggregation tool that allows users to subscribe to various blogs, news sites, and online publications.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGC_kapanga_rael</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_kapanga_rael/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 14:27:44 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_kapanga_rael/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-is-user-generated-content&#34;&gt;What is User-Generated Content?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The definition of this concept according to Deane Barker is “Content generated by non-editors, usually from the public side of the website.” (Barker, 2016).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;definition-of-user-generated-content-in-my-own-words&#34;&gt;definition of user generated content in my own words&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;User-generated content is all about the everyday person creating and sharing stuff online. . Whether it’s a funny meme, a tutorial on how to bake the perfect cake. it’s a great way for people to connect over common interests.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMS by Ben Parsons</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_parsons_ben/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 02:39:24 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_parsons_ben/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;According to Dr. Barker, content management systems are, **&amp;ldquo;A software system which automates the tasks around the management of content. A CMS assists editors in creating, organizing, controlling, securing, and ultimately delivering content.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My definition of content management systems are is a software application that allows users to create, edit, manage, and publish digital content, without needing advanced technical skills like coding.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An example of a content management system is the WordPress site that we are doing our class project on.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMS_kapanga_rael</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_kapanga_rael/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 21:02:09 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_kapanga_rael/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-a-content-management-system-cms&#34;&gt;What is a Content Management System (CMS)?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;According to Deane Barker, “A software system which automates the tasks around the management of content. A CMS assists editors in creating, organizing, controlling, securing, and ultimately delivering content.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;cms-in-my-own-words&#34;&gt;CMS in My Own Words&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A Content Management System (CMS) is a software application or platform that allows users to create, manage, and modify digital content on a website without needing extensive technical knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMS_mason_avery</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_mason_avery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 19:58:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_mason_avery/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;definition&#34;&gt;Definition&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;A software system which automates the tasks around the management of content. A CMS assists editors in creating, organizing, controlling, securing, and ultimately delivering content.&amp;rdquo; - Deane Barker&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-own-words&#34;&gt;My own words&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Content management systems or software are tools editors use to minimize the workload of content delivery and appearance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;example&#34;&gt;Example&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One real life example that I consume daily would be Google drive. Google drive allows users to create either slides, word documents or sheets. These documents are then stored, organized and presented for later use. &lt;a href=&#34;https://workspace.google.com/products/drive/&#34;&gt;https://workspace.google.com/products/drive/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content Management System Grant Lewis</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_lewis_grant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 19:58:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_lewis_grant/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;definition&#34;&gt;Definition:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“A software system which automates the tasks around the management of content. A CMS assists editors in creating, organizing, controlling, securing, and ultimately delivering content.&amp;quot; (Barker, 2016)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;self-definition&#34;&gt;Self Definition:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;this-definition-means-that-a-service-allows-users-to-organize-their-content-without-interacting-with-them-but-it-also-allows-customization-to-satisfy-the-user-if-needed&#34;&gt;This definition means that a service allows users to organize their content without interacting with them, but it also allows customization to satisfy the user if needed.&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;example&#34;&gt;Example:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This reminds me of Apple Photos as it takes the photos I have taken or imported and can self-organize them using meta-data. The Photos app will also self-make highlight reels, past trips, or topics such as family, location, date, etc. It also allows me to share, sort, and edit all my photos in folders, shared folders, and tags.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMS_mccoy_hayes</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_mccoy_hayes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 19:49:15 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_mccoy_hayes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;A software system which automates the tasks around the management of content.&#xA;A CMS assists editors in creating, organizing, controlling, securing, and&#xA;ultimately delivering content.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Deane Barker, Web Content Management Glossary&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-a-content-management-system-to-me&#34;&gt;What is a content management system to me?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To me, a content management system is a software that helps users create, manage,&#xA;edit, publish, and organize content. With a CMS you dont need to do much or any&#xA;coding; everything is there for you to plug and play.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMS_adhikari_sayana</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_adhikari_sayana/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 15:46:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_adhikari_sayana/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is CMS?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;A software system which automates the tasks around the management of content. A CMS assists editors in creating, organizing, controlling, securing, and ultimately delivering content.&amp;rdquo; (Deane Barker, Web Content Management Glossary)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In my own words&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A Content Management System is software that helps you easily create and manage website content without needing to know how to code. It provides tools for writing, editing, and organizing content, as well as controlling how the website looks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_amjad_ahmad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 15:39:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_amjad_ahmad/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;A software system which automates the tasks around the management of content. A CMS assists editors in creating, organizing, controlling, securing, and ultimately delivering content.” (The Web Content Management Glossary, Barker 2016).&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Software that&amp;rsquo;s meant to be more accesible for making content online&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(1) [https://www.squarespace.com/]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s software made for making websites and it&amp;rsquo;s main purpose is to make creating websites accesible to many, like making it easy, albeit there&amp;rsquo;s not as much functionality&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMS_Myers_Albert</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_myers_albert/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 15:30:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_myers_albert/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-content-management-systems&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Content Management Systems&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Content managemnt systems, according to Deane Barker is, &amp;ldquo;A CMS is general to managing content, regardless of format or intended purpose&amp;rdquo; (Content Management System, n.d.).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;content-management-systems-in-my-own-words&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Content Management Systems in my own words&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To me I think content management systems are systems that contain the content that is produced. Unlike content managment it doesn&amp;rsquo;t control how it is organized more so of what tools can be used at your disposal.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMS_harp_mauricio</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_harp_mauricio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 12:37:53 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_harp_mauricio/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Definition&lt;/strong&gt;: &amp;ldquo;A CMS is a software system which automates the tasks around the management of content. A CMS assists editors in creating, organizing, controlling, securing, and utimately delvering content&amp;rdquo; (Barker, 2024)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Explanation in own words&lt;/strong&gt;: I think content management system is a software tool that helps users manage digital content without needing to write code. It allows people to easily create, organize, edit, and publish website content.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Real-life example&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.apple.com/apple-news/&#34;&gt;Apple News&lt;/a&gt; is a prime example of a content management system in action. It aggregates articles from various publishers and presents them in a seamless, curated feed for users. Editors and content creators submit their articles to Apple News, and the system organizes, filters, and delivers content based on user preferences and topics.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content Management Systems?!- Omari</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_chaplin_omari/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 11:17:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_chaplin_omari/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;content-management-systems&#34;&gt;Content Management Systems&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve finally arrived at the name of the class!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A Content Management System (CMS), is defined as, &amp;ldquo;A content management system (CMS) is a software package that provides some level of automation for the tasks required to effectively manage content.&amp;rdquo; &lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To me, content management systems a tool used to gather, edit, and publish content for the purpose of efficiency and organization. They can vastly improve workflow and save tons of time, and can be flexible in their design to fit the user or company&amp;rsquo;s needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMS_Hotko_AJ</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_hotko_aj/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 17:09:52 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_hotko_aj/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;content-management-system-defined&#34;&gt;Content Management System Defined&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As defined by Deane Barker, “A software system which automates the tasks around the management of content. A CMS assists editors in creating, organizing, controlling, securing, and ultimately delivering content.” (The Web Content Management Glossary, Barker 2016).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-understanding&#34;&gt;My Understanding&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Content Management Systems or CMS’s are software that users can use in which help them deliver and organizer content. The software can be used to make creating a website or an app more efficient since a CMS would do certain parts of the process automatically allowing the user to focus on other things.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementation</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_amjad_ahmad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 15:37:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_amjad_ahmad/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Getting the essentials out the way, like assigning roles and tasks before we begin a project.&#xA;We&amp;rsquo;ll then need to make sure we document what we do, like when we complete a task.&#xA;Completed tasks will be reviewed and sent back with suggestions if needed and it&amp;rsquo;ll keep happening when complete&#xA;When all tasks are done, there will be one final review and once settled, the project is done and sent over&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementation_kemper_lea</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_kemper_lea/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 09:43:52 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_kemper_lea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In WordPress students will create blog posts and project pages as documentation to track project progress. Teams will be used for daily communications, scheduling meetings, task management, and sharing quick updates. All team members must regularly update their task manager, indicating progress, blockers, and deadlines.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementation_lewis_grant</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_lewis_grant/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 04:11:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_lewis_grant/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WordPress will be our CMS, and we will use it to manage our content, from creating and managing posts and themes to ensuring the website is consistent and that information is updated.  We will use teams to communicate and collaborate on our assigned parts and ensure others are doing their part. We also use teams to share files and task assignments.&#xA;Using WordPress, we can see what people have done or changed. The same is true for teams, as transparency with progress and tasks will help in the long run.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementation_Ilunga_victoire</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_ilunga_victoire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 01:38:14 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_ilunga_victoire/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;workflow-description&#34;&gt;Workflow description&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once everyone has taken the survey and Once tasks are assigned, We’ll use &lt;strong&gt;Microsoft Teams&lt;/strong&gt; as our communication hub where the groups members can report on their work and coordinate tasks. &lt;strong&gt;WordPress&lt;/strong&gt; will serve as our main content management system to publish and organize the content we produce.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;workflow-expectations&#34;&gt;Workflow Expectations&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Follow the Schedule and Stick to the deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Regularly check-ins with your Team and Dr.Greenhalgh.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Communicate frequently and help each other troubleshoot issues.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow implementation by Ben Parsons</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_parsons_ben/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 00:15:27 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_parsons_ben/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;using-wordpress-teams-and-other-technologies-for-workflow&#34;&gt;Using WordPress, Teams, and Other Technologies for Workflow&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WordPress&lt;/strong&gt;: We&amp;rsquo;ll use WordPress to create and publish. Everyone will draft content and submit it through WordPress.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Microsoft Teams&lt;/strong&gt;: We&amp;rsquo;ll use Microsoft Teams to brainstorm our ideas with the class and our groups. This will also be used as a type of checklist to make sure we get everything done.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other Technologies&lt;/strong&gt;: We&amp;rsquo;ll use other technologies to stay in touch with our peers outside of class to give extra feedback or ideas.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow Implementation</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_livingston_chauncey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 23:08:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_livingston_chauncey/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-will-it-be-done&#34;&gt;How will it be done?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We will have our multiple types of tasks separated into categories on Microsoft Teams, where the different groups can access them. Then, we can use those tasks to divide the work in WordPress. As far as the expectations of each person, it goes without saying that we expect everyone to do their role and, if they are struggling with their role, to ask for assistance. This can be done through teams or through our canvas shell.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementation_adhikari_sayana</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_adhikari_sayana/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 22:50:51 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_adhikari_sayana/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Implementing our workflow&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We will use WordPress, Teams, and other technologies to implement our workflow by assigning specific roles to class members and managing the content creation process. WordPress will serve as the platform where tasks like drafting, editing, and publishing content will take place. Each class member will have a designated role, such as editor, writer, or project manager, allowing us to streamline content production and ensure that responsibilities are clear. Teams will be used to communicate and collaborate, helping us set deadlines, assign tasks, and discuss progress in real-time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>implementation_Myers_Albert</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_myers_albert/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 22:50:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_myers_albert/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;workflow-description&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Workflow Description&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Teams will be used for task assignments that will be set by page. Said page can have their own &amp;ldquo;Bucket&amp;rdquo; that relates to the page. Wordpress will be used for draft pages and making sure that everything looks correct and is working before it is finalized. As well as figuring out what theme we as a class are going to use.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;expectations&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expectations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Teams: There tasks will be assigned, you are expected to complete your own tasks on time. Also, expected to help other team members out if you are done with your tasks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implimentation_kapanga_rael</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_kapanga_rael/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 22:35:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_kapanga_rael/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;implementing-our-workflow-with-wordpress&#34;&gt;Implementing Our Workflow with WordPress&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-well-use-wordpress&#34;&gt;How We’ll Use WordPress&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;WordPress is going to be our main platform for writing, editing, and publishing content. Here’s what that looks like:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Writing Posts&lt;/strong&gt;: Each of us will create our posts in WordPress and save them as drafts until they’re ready for review. We&amp;rsquo;ll use tags and categories to keep everything neat and easy to find.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reviewing Content&lt;/strong&gt;: Before anything goes live, posts will go through a review process. Editors will use WordPress to leave comments and approve or request changes. This keeps everything clear and organized.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>implementation_mason_avery</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_mason_avery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 21:27:39 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_mason_avery/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;mission&#34;&gt;Mission&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Word press will be the actual working environment we will utilize. Here we will actually edit the project and implement our brainstormed, assigned tasks. MS Teams will be how we coordinate this project between groups. Propose ideas, assign work, strategize, and the main form of class communication.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;expectations&#34;&gt;Expectations&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Every team member will be responsible for their own share. Not one member should feel expected to do everything. Team members should be expected of contributing to the overall mission, regardless of their roles. If one is struggling they should be encouraged to reach out and ask for assistance while also provide assistance whenever possible. Checking teams (or any other communication app) on a regular basis and keep the lines of communication open. If everyone is focused on their selected tasks and providing/requesting help when needed, is how we will complete this project.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementation_harp_mauricio</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_harp_mauricio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 19:45:44 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_harp_mauricio/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Use WordPress as a platform for publishing and managing content for the GMS class project. WordPress allows us to organize tasks and review posts for approval.&#xA;Microsoft Teams will serve as communication. Teams will be used to assign tasks and report on progress. Team members can update each other on the status, flag issues, and feedback on drafts before final submission.&#xA;Other technologies, like Google Docs, can be used to collaborate on drafts before moving content to WordPress for final publishing. Google Docs uses real-time editing, making the drafting and review process better.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hayes McCoy: Workflow Implementation</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_mccoy_hayes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 19:18:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_mccoy_hayes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;implementing-workflows&#34;&gt;Implementing Workflows&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;wordpress&#34;&gt;WordPress&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We will use WordPress for our content management&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Allows us to keep an eye on revision history and check what has been done and what needs&#xA;to be changed&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can leave comments on pages to provide feedback for these pages&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are so many plugins we can use to help implement a workflow, whether for collaboration, task management, automation, calandars, and&#xA;more&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;teams&#34;&gt;Teams&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We can use Teams to communicate with each other and to collaborate&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementation_Hotko_AJ</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_hotko_aj/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 13:30:44 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_hotko_aj/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;workflow-implementation&#34;&gt;Workflow Implementation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The correct implementation of Wordpress and Teams will be very beneficial to our workflow. Teams will be used for gathering ideas and turning them into tasks. There could even be different chats for different roles and elements that need to be worked on so no information gets lost. Overall, teams is going to be more of an organizational and communication factor to ensure that nobody in confused on what they need to do. Wordpress is what is going to be used in order to turn these tasks into the real thing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Management_kemper_lea</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_kemper_lea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 14:59:23 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_kemper_lea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Content management is an editorial process of creating, organizing, storing, and maintaining digital content, such as text, images, videos, and documents. The editorial process ensures that content is clear, accurate, engaging, and aligned with the intended goals. I am the content manager for the tattoo parlor I work at. So I deal with this on a daily basis. A good example of the editorial process is I will take 4 hours to make a 10-second video. A lot of editing goes into these videos for the final product to reach our audience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Management_kapanga_rael</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_kapanga_rael/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 14:30:57 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_kapanga_rael/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;content-management-definition&#34;&gt;content management definition&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;is a wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content. &lt;em&gt;(Deane barker)&lt;/em&gt;  &lt;a href=&#34;https://spencergreenhalgh.com/_302_2024_w6_c1.html#57&#34;&gt;classes slides&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;. In my own word, content management is all about organizing, storing, and sharing information and media (like text, images, and videos) in a way that makes it easy for people to access and use. This can involve using tools and software to create, edit, and publish content on websites or social media. Essentially, it&amp;rsquo;s about making sure the right content gets to the right people at the right time!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementation_coleman_bryan</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_coleman_bryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 13:19:09 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_coleman_bryan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We will use WordPress, Teams, and other technologies to &lt;strong&gt;implement our workflow&lt;/strong&gt; by instilling a process of steps to help implement workflow. Primarily, WordPress can be used for content management as we can use this program to put each student in their chosen roles, such as an editor or project manager. We can then utilize Teams to help create communication lines between the various groups and roles as well as creating deadlines for when we need assignments completed by. These processes can help create a seamless workflow that enhances productivity and collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMS_bryant_henry</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_bryant_henry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 11:20:07 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_bryant_henry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-a-content-management-system&#34;&gt;What is a Content Management System?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In &lt;em&gt;Web Content Management&lt;/em&gt;, author Deane Barker defines a content management system (CMS) as a &amp;ldquo;software system that automates the tasks around the management of content&amp;rdquo;. CMSs help content editors with &amp;ldquo;controlling, securing, and ultimately delivering content&amp;rdquo; (Barker, 2016).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In other words, this means that a content management system is a technology that allows a webmaster, website creator, or website administrator to create content and display it to users. CMSs make it so a user doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to follow many steps, they just have to use the CMS, and content can be created and deployed automatically.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMS_chen_ricky</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_chen_ricky/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 11:15:52 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_chen_ricky/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-content-management-system&#34;&gt;What is Content Management System?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;According to Deane Barker, &amp;ldquo;A software system which autmates the tasks around the management of content. A CMS assists editors in creating, organizing, controlling, securing, and ultimately delivering content.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Barker, D.(2016). &lt;a href=&#34;https://deanebarker.net/tech/glossary/content-management-system/&#34;&gt;Web Content Management Glossary&lt;/a&gt; O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;to-my-understanding&#34;&gt;To my Understanding&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Content management system is a platform that holds the content that people are publicly seeing. Its a easier way for people who dont know how to code to show their content on the web.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementation_chen_ricky</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_chen_ricky/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 10:55:11 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_chen_ricky/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-utilize-our-tools&#34;&gt;How to utilize our tools&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, everyone takes the roles survey and gets assigned a role they&amp;rsquo;re comfortable with&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Second, with the tasks in the teams group, Dr. Greenhalgh assigns each member a task. OR every member go in the get a task they like and complete their task then move on to the next one&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Third, after the task is complete, mark it complete, type a descrption or screenshot of the result and put it in Teams.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>implementation_bryant_henry</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_bryant_henry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 10:54:55 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_bryant_henry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;workflow-description&#34;&gt;Workflow Description&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, we will post the required tasks to Microsoft Teams, moving them into the &amp;ldquo;Brainstorming&amp;rdquo; section on Teams first. Once the tasks have been brainstormed, they will be assigned to the relevant teams for drafting. Once the groups have drafted their work, the assigned project manager people will look it over and then show it to Dr. Greenhalgh for final feedback. If feedback is made, it will be fixed by the editors or designers before being finalized and actually implemented on the website.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMS_nguyen_nhi</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_nguyen_nhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 10:53:07 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_nguyen_nhi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;definition&#34;&gt;Definition&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;A software system which automates the tasks around the management of content. A CMS assists editors in creating, organizing, controlling, securing, and ultimately delivering content.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Deane Barker, Web Content Management Glossary&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In other words, a CMS lets you build and run a website without having to be a web developer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;example&#34;&gt;Example&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A example of a CMS is my favorite recipe blog, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.allrecipes.com/recipe/12682/apple-pie-by-grandma-ople/&#34;&gt;Apple Pie by Grandma Ople&lt;/a&gt;. The person running the blog can add new recipes, edit old ones, and organize all the content in categories like “pie” or “cakes.”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>implementation_nguyen_nhi</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_nguyen_nhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 10:53:07 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_nguyen_nhi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-implement-our-workflow&#34;&gt;How to implement our workflow&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We will use WordPress and Teams to help our class stay organized and connected. WordPress will be where students can share their work and updates. We will post our updates about our progress and that will allow everyone to stay informed about what others are doing. We also use Teams to assign tasks so that everyone knows what they are responsible for.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;expectation&#34;&gt;Expectation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Group members should check in with each other to share progress. Attendance at meetings is important and we should report the outcomes of these meetings.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow_Kemer_Lea</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_kemer_lea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 10:51:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_kemer_lea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For our GMS class project to ensure that the task is completed properly we must break it into workflow phases such as planning, executing, and reviewing. In the planning stage, we will define our task and objectives outlining what &amp;ldquo;completion&amp;rdquo; of our website will look like. Delegation of tasks is also a part of the planning phase. Execution is actual work on the task to ensure that we are on track and identify any issues. In the reviewing stage any necessary revisions or adjustments based on the peer review and feedback. We compare our planning to see if we have hit all of the objectives then the task is complete.  To delegate workload the Planners and Editors (6-7 people) should be the same people, that way they can envision the project and be the ones at the end to revise the draft. We should have 7-10 individuals working on the body of information. A group of 3-4 working on the presentation of our site. We should have leaders of each subgroup speak on behalf of the group for update meetings.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>management_lewis_grant</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_lewis_grant/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 04:10:52 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_lewis_grant/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;“A wide-ranging term that generally refers to defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content. - Deane Barker, Flying Squirrel Glossary&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What is content management to me? From the quote above, CM is how content is organized and presented. This can be due to how the content is organized, stored, and delivered to a person. Beyond that, with content management, it could also mean who gets to see the content and who can&amp;rsquo;t.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow by Ben Parsons</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_parsons_ben/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 00:30:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_parsons_ben/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;According to Deane Barker content management is, &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;A wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content.&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Content managment to me means, the management of man made entertainment, information, etc that is meant to be consumed by humans.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An example of content management is a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wix.com/&#34;&gt;Wix template&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a good example of content management because you are able to manage information and have it organized using a website template from Wix.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defining Content Management</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_livingston_chauncey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 22:56:46 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_livingston_chauncey/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-it&#34;&gt;What is it?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Content Management is referred to as&#xA;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;A wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Deane Barker, Flying Squirrel Glossary.&lt;/em&gt; In my opinion it just means that there is information that is being organized or controlled using an editorial method.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-does-it-look-like&#34;&gt;What does it look like?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We see examples of content management every day, especially on social media. This &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/&#34;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt; to YouTube showcases multiple videos aka content and it is managed because it was engineered to display the content in a way that benefits the user.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Management_donnelly_matthew</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_donnelly_matthew/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 22:43:29 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_donnelly_matthew/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-content-management&#34;&gt;What is content management?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Deane Barker says that content management is the “practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content” (Barker 2016).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;in-my-own-words&#34;&gt;In my own words&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would say that content management is a way to make viewing and navigating websites easier, for users and for the creators of that website as well. It is a way of organzing types of content on websites.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;example&#34;&gt;Example&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a photographer and youtuber that I watch all the time, he even has his own website. &lt;a href=&#34;https://gxace.com/&#34;&gt;GxAce&lt;/a&gt; he has a shop where you can buy lightroom presents, a contact page and even a focal length calculator. All of these things go together with content management because he is organzing his content for buyers and fans to view.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hayes McCoy: Define Content Management</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_mccoy_hayes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 20:13:26 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_mccoy_hayes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;A wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating,&#xA;organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Deane Barker, Flying Squirrel Glossary&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-content-management-to-me&#34;&gt;What Is Content Management To Me?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To me, content management is the way that content is planned, organized, structured, edited, and delivered.&#xA;Content management, essentially, is just managing content.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-an-example-of-this&#34;&gt;What Is An Example Of This?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An example that I thought of when thinking about content management was YouTube.&#xA;The process of running a YouTube channel follows all of the practices of content&#xA;management defined by Deane Barker. The specific YouTube channel that I thought of was&#xA;is the channel Good Mythical Morning.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Managament</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_ahmad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 20:13:26 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_ahmad/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;“A wide-randing term that generally refers to the practie of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content.”Barker, D.(2016). Flying Squirrel Glossary. O’Reilly Media&#xA;Self-explanatory, how you handle content, like sorting, archiving, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Take GameFAQs for example, where users posts are organized by things like categories, subforums, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[hi] (&lt;a href=&#34;https://gamefaqs.gamespot.com/&#34;&gt;https://gamefaqs.gamespot.com/&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;They use content managament by letting users sorting posts (Ex. Views), pages, etc. and they let them manage their posts, like editing them&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Management_harp_mauricio</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_harp_mauricio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 19:08:19 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_harp_mauricio/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Definition&lt;/strong&gt;: Content management is a wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content&amp;quot; (Barker, 2024)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Explanation in own words&lt;/strong&gt;: Content management involves handling every step of the content lifecycle, from planning and creating to reviewing, organizing, and delivering it to the audience&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Real-life example&lt;/strong&gt;: I use &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com&#34;&gt;YouTube&lt;/a&gt;, an example of content management. YouTube creators upload and manage their videos, organized through channels and search algorithms.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Management_mason_avery</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_mason_avery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 16:55:51 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_mason_avery/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;definition&#34;&gt;Definition&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;lsquo;A wide-ranging term that generally rerfers to the practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing and delivering content&amp;rsquo;- Deane Barker&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-own-words&#34;&gt;My own words&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Content management is the organization of content in regards to its particular users and specific practices.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;example&#34;&gt;Example&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Reddit is a content management system that allows users to contribute to what they call &amp;ldquo;communities&amp;rdquo; and organizes their posts to those specific threads. Links &amp;lsquo;hot&amp;rsquo; topics and recommends other communities to authors/users that may be interested.&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reddit.com/&#34;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Management_adhikari_sayana</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_adhikari_sayana/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 15:30:37 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_adhikari_sayana/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is content management?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;A wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating, oraganizing,securing,reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content.&amp;rdquo; (Deane Barker, Flying Squirrel Glossary)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In my own words&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Content management is the process of handling digital content, from creating and editing to organizing and publishing it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Example&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.shopify.com/&#34;&gt;Shopify&lt;/a&gt; is a widely known content management system specifically designed for e-commerce. It allows users to create and manage online stores, providing tools for product management, payment processing, and order fulfillment, making it easier for businesses to sell products online.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Management_Hotko_AJ</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_hotko_aj/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 14:16:18 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_hotko_aj/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;content-management-defined&#34;&gt;Content Management Defined&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“A wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content.” (The Web Content Management Glossary, Barker 2016).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-take-on-content-management&#34;&gt;My Take on Content Management&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Content Management is the way that we generally organize our content in a manner in which is the most logical and efficient.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;example-of-content-management&#34;&gt;Example of Content Management&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/document/u/0/&#34;&gt;Google Docs&lt;/a&gt; would be an example of content management, you can create docs in which they are organized by date or name. Create your own documents putting content within them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Management_Myers_Albert</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_myers_albert/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 12:30:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_myers_albert/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-content-management&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Content Management&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Content managemnt, according to Deane Barker is, &amp;ldquo;a wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;content-management-in-my-own-words&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Content Management in my own words&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To me I think content management is the content is organized for the consumer to see in a certain way. You could easily just put out unorganized content. However, people probably won&amp;rsquo;t want to view it, if there is no fluid motion of your content.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Management_Ilunga_victoire</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_ilunga_victoire/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 11:59:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_ilunga_victoire/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;definition-of-content-management&#34;&gt;Definition of content management&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;content management&#xA;A wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content (Barker, Flying Squirrel Glossary).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;in-simple-words&#34;&gt;In simple words&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Content management is basically how we organize and handle digital content, like articles, videos, or images, to make sure it&amp;rsquo;s easy for people to find and use. It includes everything from creating and editing content, to storing and publishing it on platforms like websites or apps.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Content Management?- Omari</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_chaplin_omari/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 10:26:39 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_chaplin_omari/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;content-management&#34;&gt;Content Management&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our slides define &amp;ldquo;content management&amp;rdquo; as, &amp;ldquo;A wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content.&amp;rdquo; - &lt;a href=&#34;https://deanebarker.net/tech/glossary/content-management/&#34;&gt;Deane Barker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For me, I think of content managment as the thing that we or a team do to create, manage, manipulate, and organize the content we produce or otherwise have authority over. We make choices and decisions that we can make that will change how this content exists.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>management_nguyen_nhi</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_nguyen_nhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 10:26:39 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_nguyen_nhi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;content-management&#34;&gt;Content management&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Definition &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;A wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content.&lt;/em&gt; - Deane Barker, Flying Squirrel Glossary&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In other words, &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Content management is how we handle the information we share on websites and apps. It&amp;rsquo;s all about keeping everything in order so people can find what they need easily.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;example&#34;&gt;Example:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A example of content management is Netflix. They add new movies and TV shows, organize them by genre, and update recommendations based on what users watch. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.netflix.com&#34;&gt;Netflix&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow_harp_mauricio</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_harp_mauricio/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 22:33:35 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_harp_mauricio/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For our GMS class project, a content management workflow that follows several phases to ensure tasks are completed. First, the project manager assigns tasks based on the team&amp;rsquo;s needs. The content creator develops the content. Once completed, the content moves into the review phase, where another team member checks for accuracy and alignment with project goals. An editor refines the content, ensuring it is ready for submission. The final approvers does one last check before the content is published or submitted.&#xA;Roles -  Project manager (who oversees tasks and timelines), Content creators, Reviewers, Editors, Final approvers, and Tech support (for managing technical issues related to publishing)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>management_chen_ricky</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_chen_ricky/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 11:22:45 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_chen_ricky/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;content-management-definiton&#34;&gt;Content Management Definiton&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;According to Deane Barker, &amp;ldquo;A wide-randing term that generally refers to the practie of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Barker, D.(2016). &lt;a href=&#34;https://deanebarker.net/books/squirrel/the-basics/&#34;&gt;Flying Squirrel Glossary&lt;/a&gt;. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In My Own Words&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To my understanding, content management is something a human do make sure what they&amp;rsquo;re publishing is understandable to other humans.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;content-management-example&#34;&gt;Content Management Example&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An exmaple of content is news articles. News article is something a human has to create, organize, review, approve, published, and finally deliver to the public. This is a news article about hurricane Helene, a human was there to capture the pictures, then most likely a different human created and edited the post, then got approved, then published. Finally other people can see the news. The site is managing the content for all of the news articles.&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://abcnews.go.com/US/live-updates/hurricane-helene/?id=113931821&#34;&gt;Hurricane Helene&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>management_bryant_henry</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_bryant_henry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 10:55:07 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_bryant_henry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-content-management&#34;&gt;What is Content Management?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In &lt;em&gt;Flying Squirrel Glossary&lt;/em&gt;, author Deane Barker defines content management as a &amp;ldquo;wide-ranging&amp;rdquo; term that refers to the &amp;ldquo;practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content&amp;rdquo; (Barker, 2016).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In other words, this means that content management is the process of working with and processing the content that a user sees on a particular platform before the user gets to see the content.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation_Ilunga_victoire</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_ilunga_victoire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:51:32 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_ilunga_victoire/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;definition&#34;&gt;Definition&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot; The general concept and processes around modifying content for display in a particular channel, usaually through templating. A template apllied will result in output which is then delivered.&amp;quot; -Deanne Barker, *web content management glossary&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;in-my-own-words&#34;&gt;In my own words&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Presentation is how content is adapted and displayed depending on the platform. This is done by applying templates that determine the structure and layout of the content.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;example&#34;&gt;Example&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Canva&lt;/strong&gt;. Canva is an online tool for graphic design that helps users create different types of visual content. It offers templates for things like social media posts, presentations, and posters. For example, a template for a social media post will look different from a presentation slide, even if they have the same text or images. Canva makes it easy for users to adjust their content for different visual formats, ensuring that the design works well for each specific platform.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation_Ilunga_victoire</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_ilunga_victoire2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:51:32 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_ilunga_victoire2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;definition&#34;&gt;Definition&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot; The general concept and processes around modifying content for display in a particular channel, usaually through templating. A template apllied will result in output which is then delivered.&amp;quot; -Deanne Barker, *web content management glossary&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;in-my-own-words&#34;&gt;In my own words&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Presentation is how content is adapted and displayed depending on the platform. This is done by applying templates that determine the structure and layout of the content.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;example&#34;&gt;Example&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Canva&lt;/strong&gt;. Canva is an online tool for graphic design that helps users create different types of visual content. It offers templates for things like social media posts, presentations, and posters. For example, a template for a social media post will look different from a presentation slide, even if they have the same text or images. Canva makes it easy for users to adjust their content for different visual formats, ensuring that the design works well for each specific platform.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worflow_Ilunga_Victoire</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_ilunga_victoire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:51:32 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_ilunga_victoire/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;phases&#34;&gt;Phases&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, we will start by defining our project objectives so everyone understands what we want to accomplish. Then, we will break down the project into smaller tasks and assign them based on each person’s strengths. Then we should set deadlines to keep us on track and ensures timely completion.&#xA;Once tasks are completed, we’ll compile drafts for review to get feddbacks from everyone.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;roles&#34;&gt;Roles&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;project manager&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;content creators&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Editors&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Developers&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow Proposal</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_livingston_chauncey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 23:48:14 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_livingston_chauncey/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;task-phases&#34;&gt;Task Phases&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think there should be couple phases for the tasks starting with deciding what the task is and how indepth it will be. Next, we should decide which part of the website the task belongs to, is it part fo the main home page or is it part of an external link? Once that&amp;rsquo;s figured out that will determine who it goes to and they can begin to work on it. Once their done we&amp;rsquo;ll do a review and make sure it is correct and functional and go from there.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow_kapanga_rael</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_kapanga_rael/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 20:38:39 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_kapanga_rael/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;content creation work flow:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before starting to work on our class project, we should consider the following steps:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Brain storming&lt;/em&gt;: This is where content ideas are brainstormed, aligned with overall goals, and scheduled.&#xA;&lt;em&gt;Content Creation&lt;/em&gt;: this is where we start creating content after brainstorming our ideas.&#xA;&lt;em&gt;Review &amp;amp; Editing&lt;/em&gt;: after creating our content, we review the content for accuracy, grammar, and overall quality.&#xA;&lt;em&gt;Approval &amp;amp; Final Review&lt;/em&gt;: after we have edited and review the content, we will have stakeholders take a look at the content for a final review and approve the content.&#xA;&lt;em&gt;Publication&lt;/em&gt;: and lastly is the publication of the content, The content is uploaded to the website.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow_adhikari_sayana</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_adhikari_sayana/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 19:59:53 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_adhikari_sayana/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WORKFLOW PHASES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Plannig Phase:&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;In this phase,the task is clearly defined. The goals, deadlines, and required deliverables are identified. Roles are assigned to classmates, and expectations are set.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Creating Phase:&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;In this phase we produce the content itself, whether it&amp;rsquo;s writing, designing visuals, or creating multimedia.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reviewing Phase:&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;After the content is created, it is passed to one or more reviewers for feedback. This phase ensures that the content is accurate, aligns with project goals, and meets quality standards.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow_Hotko_AJ</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_hotko_aj/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 19:04:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_hotko_aj/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;workflow&#34;&gt;Workflow&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When considering the different phases that a task must pass through until it is completed, it would be best to determine when this task needs to be completed. A hard deadline is important because people need to know how to organize themselves in such a manner so that they will have the task completed on time. It would be best to consider even putting that deadline before it actually needs to be done just in case something is to go wrong. Once the deadline is confirmed, it would be best to make sure what exactly the task is, this would be making sure that it is clear what needs to be accomplished. Next, any prior research that needs to be done should be looked into since working on the task and researching at the same time could lead to errors. Once research is complete, it would be wise to break down the task into steps allowing for an even clearer visualization of what needs to be done. Depending on the size of the task you could even set deadlines for yourself to keep on track to meeting the deadline. Once there is enough research and preparation you could finally begin the task, while working on the task taking notes on what has been created or changed. This is important in that if someone else needs to do something similar it will be done in the same manner which would be more efficient. Once the task is completed, it would be a good idea to go over it and make sure everything is correct and up to standard, even referencing the steps to complete the task to make sure you got what you needed to get done.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow by Ben Parsons</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_parsons_ben/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 15:13:06 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_parsons_ben/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;workflow-phases&#34;&gt;Workflow Phases&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Task Assignment&lt;/strong&gt;: Tasks are distributed to class members with clear objectives and deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Content Creation&lt;/strong&gt;: Assigned members develop content (writing, media, etc.).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Review&lt;/strong&gt;: Peer review for feedback on quality and accuracy.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revisions&lt;/strong&gt;: Adjustments made based on feedback.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Approval&lt;/strong&gt;: Final content approval by the editor.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Publication&lt;/strong&gt;: Content is posted on the class blog.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;roles&#34;&gt;Roles&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Task Manager&lt;/strong&gt;: Assigns tasks and ensures deadlines are met.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Content Creators&lt;/strong&gt;: Produce the assigned content.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reviewers&lt;/strong&gt;: Review content for feedback.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Editor&lt;/strong&gt;: Reviews and approves final content.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Publisher&lt;/strong&gt;: Publishes the approved content on the platform.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This structured and organized workflow makes sure that all tasks are completed efficiently and all members contribute to high-quality content.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow_lewis_grant</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_lewis_grant/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 14:06:03 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_lewis_grant/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When creating a workflow, the main focus is fixing an issue or problem or working towards a specific goal. By determining our goal first, we can build a fine-tuned system towards our goal.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Setting clear deadlines and determining the sequence of tasks is crucial. This ensures that each part of the project is completed on time. If one team or group falls behind, it could potentially disrupt the entire project.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow_Myers_Albert</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_myers_albert/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 13:48:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_myers_albert/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Process to complete a task&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, figure out what the timeline on how long it will take to do said task. Second, figure out who needs to do what part and who is most effecient in said task. Third, Give everyojne their assignemnts and a deadline for said assignments to be done. Now of course some people might rely on one part of a task being done before they can start, so make sure you have the correct priority set up. Fourh, review the completed task and as a team make sure everyone is in agreement with the finshed product. If not, go through and make the changes all together. Fifth, make sure task can be fully functionaly and then fix the little things as you go. Lastly, make sure everything works flawlessly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMS_coleman_bryan</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_coleman_bryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 10:28:01 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_coleman_bryan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A &lt;strong&gt;content management system (CMS)&lt;/strong&gt; is software that helps users create, manage, and modify content on a website without the need for technical knowledge. I got the definition from &lt;a href=&#34;https://kinsta.com/knowledgebase/content-management-system/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&#xA;In my own words, a content management system is software that can help a user when it comes to creating and publishing any type of content.&#xA;For my example, I think Wix serves as a great content management system as it helps a user create, manage, and publish content. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wix.com/?utm_source=google&amp;amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;amp;utm_campaign=20529976750%5E157109364910%5Esearch%20-%20wix&amp;amp;experiment_id=wix%5Ee%5E710272803327%5E&amp;amp;gad_source=1&amp;amp;gclid=Cj0KCQjw3vO3BhCqARIsAEWblcA007uhh_p0Cb0RSPnWsaJmdvvuA670qoCoBVsCctGd_EPZPbSf00saAs9vEALw_wcB&#34;&gt;Here is my link to the website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Can We Effectively Manage Our Content? - Omari</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_chaplin_omari/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 10:26:39 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_chaplin_omari/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;content-management-proposal&#34;&gt;Content Management Proposal&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Well, its that part of the semester!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When thinking about the workflow for our blog, we&amp;rsquo;ll have to consider an approach that has as little friction as possible as we make decisions on how we complete tasks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Task/Prompt&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Find out what our task is, based on instructions and vision for the blog.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Idea Formation and Brainstorming&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With a task/prompt in mind, we can begin to think about ideas of what we want to post. This step may be fairly quick or automatic depending on the complexity of the task/prompt. &lt;em&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s critical that we find an objective to follow in our next step.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Management_coleman_bryan</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_coleman_bryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 10:16:53 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_coleman_bryan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Content management&lt;/strong&gt; is a wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content.&#xA;I got this definition from &lt;a href=&#34;https://spencergreenhalgh.com/_302_2024_w6_c1.html#50&#34;&gt;the class slides&lt;/a&gt;.&#xA;In my own words, content management is the collection, management, and publication of any form of information or content through a platform.&#xA;For my example, I think WordPress serves as a great example of content management. I say this as WordPress allows users to create, edit, and manage their content, which directly lines up with the definition of content management. &lt;a href=&#34;https://gms.spencergreenhalgh.com/wp-admin/&#34;&gt;Here is the link for WordPress.&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow_coleman_bryan</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_coleman_bryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 10:00:33 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_coleman_bryan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When looking at the &lt;strong&gt;different phases&lt;/strong&gt; a task should move through before it is complete, I believe it can primarily broken down as we can begin by defining the problem and the objectives along with it. Next, we should plan out the schedule and see if certain aspects need to be done by a certain deadline. Next, any minor background research that needs to be done before completing the task can occur, and then they will actually carry out the task and fix it. After that, it would be useful to minored the changes and almost test it to make sure it works as intended. To conclude this process, we should end by getting feedback to see if we could improve our work next time. Additionally, when looking at the different roles people in the class should take on, I believe it would most effective to do a mix of both permanent jobs as well as on the fly changes. When it comes to permanent jobs, I believe having an overall project manager to oversee everything would be very effective for keeping everyone on task. However, I believe most tasks should be completed by those most educated on those specific subjects or if an individual has a desire to take it. In other words, let every individual play to their strengths and around their weaknesses. In other words, we can change the editors, site planners, developers, and administrators as we need to.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Project Proposal</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_mason_avery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:09:25 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_mason_avery/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;tasks-phases&#34;&gt;Tasks phases&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Assuming we utilize Microsoft teams and with the introduction of the &amp;ldquo;Bucket-System&amp;rdquo; Dr. Greenhalgh showcased. I propose we split the tasks sections into 5-6 buckets.&#xA;1st Bucket - General idea, or initial thought of something&#xA;2nd Bucket - Planning stage&#xA;3rd Bucket - assignment stage (delegating task to who should be responsible)&#xA;4th Bucket - Finished state (task is finished and ready to be integrated)&#xA;5th Bucket - Revision stage (review work for potential errors)&#xA;6th Bucket - Completed tab (to track what has been fully developed and finished)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_amjad_ahmad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_amjad_ahmad/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;order&#34;&gt;Order&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1, Determine goals&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2, Make schedule and set tasks, like a roadmap&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;3, Check in every now and then&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;4, Rough draft state&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;5, Get input&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;6, Continue working&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;7, Work on final draft&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;8, Review&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;9, Finish&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;some-roles&#34;&gt;Some roles&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Owner, co-owner, leader, worker, and manager&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation_Kemper_Lea</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_kemper_lea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:32:09 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_kemper_lea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Content presentation is how information (or content) is structured, displayed, and formatted for users in various mediums, such as websites, apps, or printed materials. Focusing on the visual aspects of the content delivery such as design, typography, organization, interactive elements, and media inclusion/placement. Basically how information is shown to you, whether on a website, in an app, or print. A good example of presentation in my everyday use is the dark mode feature on Instagram/Facebook.&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/marketplace/?ref=app_tab&#34;&gt;my link&lt;/a&gt; With the quick change of a setting, I can make the content more aesthetically easy to consume. Dark mode can also reduce brightness and glare serving as a more comfortable viewing option. In light or dark mode, the text, images, and videos remain identical showing a distinction between content and presentation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_Kemper_Lea</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_kemper_lea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:29:55 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_kemper_lea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Content aggregation is the organization of content from various sources (websites, blogs, and social media) onto a single platform. Allowing users to access a variety of information in one place. An example of content aggregation is Lex 18 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.lex18.com/&#34;&gt;my link&lt;/a&gt; our local news channel. They have many different articles that are linked on the first page. If you click on the headline it will reroute you to that article. In addition to written content, the page also includes videos, headline stories, and a link to watch the live news show. This blend of multimedia makes their site easily navigable, making to so you don&amp;rsquo;t have to visit multiple sites to get up to date news.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ugc_Kemper_Lea</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_kemper_lea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:22:56 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_kemper_lea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;User-generated content is images, videos, messages, or social media posts that are created and shared by human users. These messages are produced and shared by individuals rather than organizations or brands. An example of user-generated content is a review left on a brand by users, reflecting their genuine experiences, opinions, and feedback about said brand.&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.google.com/search?(q=524+angliana+reviews&amp;amp;sca_esv=0e45d3c299f99f39&amp;amp;sca_upv=1&amp;amp;rlz=1C5CHFA_enUS948US954&amp;amp;sxsrf=ADLYWIJ5KSMnFXihWz04jAa2DhgLqkw-HA%3A1726527509159&amp;amp;ei=FbjoZpufCZ2V5OMP-OWh6A0&amp;amp;ved=0ahUKEwjb_YKXyMiIAxWdCnkGHfhyCN0Q4dUDCBA&amp;amp;uact=5&amp;amp;oq=524+angliana+reviews&amp;amp;gs_lp=Egxnd3Mtd2l6LXNlcnAiFDUyNCBhbmdsaWFuYSByZXZpZXdzMg4QLhiABBjHARiOBRivATIGEAAYFhgeMgYQABgWGB4yCxAAGIAEGIYDGIoFMgsQABiABBiGAxiKBTILEAAYgAQYhgMYigUyCBAAGIAEGKIEMggQABiABBiiBDIIEAAYgAQYogQyCBAAGIAEGKIEMh0QLhiABBjHARiOBRivARiXBRjcBBjeBBjgBNgBAUjCGlDnAlirFnABeAGQAQCYAYsBoAHWB6oBAzAuOLgBA8gBAPgBAZgCCaACnAjCAgoQABiwAxjWBBhHwgINEAAYgAQYsAMYQxiKBcICEBAuGIAEGLADGEMY1AIYigXCAh8QLhiABBiwAxhDGNQCGMcBGMgDGIoFGI4FGK8B2AEBwgIcEC4YgAQYsAMYQxjHARjIAxiKBRiOBRivAdgBAcICFhAuGIAEGLADGEMY1AIYyAMYigXYAQHCAgUQABiABJgDAIgGAZAGEboGBggBEAEYCJIHAzEuOKAHuEk&amp;amp;sclient=gws-wiz-serp#lrd=0x884244991696ba75:0xd966afd35c1c1a51,1,,,,&#34;&gt;my link&lt;/a&gt;All of these negative reviews are supposed to warn off other potential clients for this apartment. I left a negative review participating in user-generated content intending my message to be seen by other users.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow_mccoy_hayes</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_mccoy_hayes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:06:28 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_mccoy_hayes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;phases-a-task-should-pass-through&#34;&gt;Phases a Task Should Pass Through&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before any piece of content gets published, it should be throughly&#xA;gone over until it is determined complete. Below is an idea of my on how&#xA;we could structure these phases:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Planning Phase&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We need to define our goals.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We need to get input from our peers and client.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We need to see what we have to work with, and overview what is already there.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Designing Phase&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We need to create basic layouts of our ideas.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We need to plan out the structure of the task.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We need to agree on design elements and things like colors, fonts, and other visual aspects.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Development Phase&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We need to gather and transfer information from the old site to the new one.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We need to focus on the front-end and back-end development related to the task.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We need to make sure that everything works as intended.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Testing Phase&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We need to test to make sure the completed task is functional.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We need to make changes based on test findings.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Review Phase&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We need to review what we have done with our peers and decide if we need to change anything.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We need to review with our professor and implement any changes that are suggested.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Task Implementation Phase&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If the task successfully completes all prior tasks and is approved then the task should be implemented and considered complete.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Continuous Editing Phase&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If for some reason a task is affected by another task or something changes where the task needs implemented differently,&#xA;the task should be changed accordingly.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;roles-to-consider&#34;&gt;Roles to Consider&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are many different roles that come into play when designing a website. For our class,&#xA;I have come up with some roles to consider for people to take on during this project.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>workflow_chen_ricky</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_chen_ricky/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 12:16:55 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_chen_ricky/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;phases-to-pass-through&#34;&gt;Phases to Pass Through&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, identify the problem/goal, know the what is the final goal of this task&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Second, braindstorm ideas and assigning the right person for this specific task&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Third, drafts should be made including the different ideas in he brainstorm&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fourth, an editor/publisher should review the final draft to make edits, suggestion, etc&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Finally, post into the site after majorities&amp;rsquo;s approval&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;roles&#34;&gt;Roles&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Roles will be important to increase the effiency of the workflow. We will need a contributor role, someone who writes the drafts. An editor role, someone who edits the drafts from contributor, whether it&amp;rsquo;s spelling check, grammar, making it make sense. A admin role who manages everything to make sure nothing in the site goes wrong. The admin role will also be the one to approve everything. Finally a designer in the site will help visually appealing for the audience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation_harp_mauricio</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_harp_mauricio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 11:07:09 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_harp_mauricio/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Definition&lt;/strong&gt; - The general concept and processes around modifying content for display in a particular channel, usually through templating. A template applied to content will result in output which is then delivered&amp;quot; (Barker, 2024)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Explain in Your Own Word&lt;/strong&gt; - Presentation refers to how information is formatted and displayed using templates&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Example&lt;/strong&gt; - [Netflix] (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.netflix.com&#34;&gt;https://www.netflix.com&lt;/a&gt;) presents the same movies, shows in different ways depending on your device, such as a smartphone, TV, or web browser.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentstion_kapanga_rael</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentstion_kapanga_rael/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:54:50 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentstion_kapanga_rael/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;presentation&#34;&gt;Presentation:&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;according to barker, presentation is specificaly the the visual elements of a piece of content that are displayed on devices and other channels to provide a specific experience for the user.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;presentation-in-my-own-term&#34;&gt;Presentation in my own term:&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Presentation refers to how information is structured and communicated to an audience. It involves the use of organization, design, and style to make the content more accessible and engaging.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;example-of-a-presentation&#34;&gt;example of a presentation&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A great example of effective presentation is  &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wikipedia.org/&#34;&gt;Wikipedia’s main page&lt;/a&gt;. Every Wikipedia article follows a clear, consistent structure: it starts with a brief introduction or summary, followed by sectioned content that expands on the topic&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation_Hotko_AJ</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_hotko_aj/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:43:03 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_hotko_aj/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;presentation-defined&#34;&gt;Presentation Defined&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“The general concept and processes around modifying content for displaying in a particular channel, usually through templating. A template applied to content will result in output which is then delivered.” (Barker, 2016).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-definition-of-presentation&#34;&gt;My definition of Presentation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I see presentation as the visual appearance of content and how it can be formatted in different ways.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;example-of-presentation&#34;&gt;Example of Presentation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An example of presentation would be looking at how news articles on websites are presented. On the &lt;a href=&#34;https://news.google.com/home?hl=en-US&amp;amp;gl=US&amp;amp;ceid=US:en&#34;&gt;google news&lt;/a&gt; home page we can see pictures and summaries of different articles. Once we click on an article that we would like to read we notice that the content is the same as the summary plus some more information. The only real difference is that the presentation has changed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>workflow_bryant_henry</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_bryant_henry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:42:55 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_bryant_henry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;different-phases&#34;&gt;Different Phases&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are several different phases that a task should pass through before it is marked complete. First, the task should be brainstormed; we should actually think about what we want to work on with the site. The brainstorming step would also include assigning someone to work on the post. Next, once the task has been brainstormed, we need to actually draft the task - we need to fix the site in whatever way we brainstormed about. Then, someone should look over the fix and make sure that it meets what was discussed in the brainstorming and publish it if it meets these outlines. Finally, the task can be implemented, or published to the site, or displayed, or whatever.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation_lewis_grant</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_lewis_grant/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 04:10:52 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_lewis_grant/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Content is the raw data, while presentation is how it&amp;rsquo;s shown.&amp;rdquo; -Mauricio Harp.&#xA;For me, the quote by Mauricio Harp best explains what a presentation is. I would also say it can be how information is represented, such as charts or visuals, as well as text, in an easy way to communicate an idea.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One instance for me is the news app on my phone. Of course, writers could post articles without formatting. But by doing so, they make the content engaging and grab people&amp;rsquo;s attention. They add charts or visuals. I can say that presentation can change how people interact with content; for example, if I read an article on space, including a picture, it grabs my attention and can drive me or another reader to learn more about the topic.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation_parsons_ben</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_parsons_ben/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:46:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_parsons_ben/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;According to Deane Barker Presentation is, &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;The general concept and processes around modifying content for display in a particular channel, usually through templating. A template applied to content will result in output which is then delivered.&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo;&amp;quot;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To me, presentation is something where content is organized together to share information about something at once.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An example of presention is &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1qUirMmzA__i5-y8k8ugkhJDx31sJ3JVs1z8wyC0lUjs/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;this link&lt;/a&gt; of a presentation I was apart of.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is relevant to my definition because it is a way to share different types of information and content at the same time in a certain format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation Avery M</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_mason_avery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:09:25 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_mason_avery/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;presentation&#34;&gt;Presentation&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;content is the raw data, while presentation is how it&amp;rsquo;s shown&amp;rdquo; Mauricio Harp&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-presentation-to-me-in-regards-to-content&#34;&gt;What is presentation to me in regards to content&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To myself, like Mauricio points out, presentation is the visuals of content. The way the content is portrayed and how its viewed. I think of it like taking a picture. For example, I could take a picture of my physical computer monitor using my cellphone but visually the image will be distorted and unclear compared to a screenshot.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defining Presentation</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_livingston_chauncey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 22:25:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_livingston_chauncey/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-presentation-and-what-does-it-look-like&#34;&gt;What is Presentation and what does it look like?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Usually associated with &lt;a href=&#34;https://ict302fall24.netlify.app/posts/content_livingston_chauncey/&#34;&gt;content&lt;/a&gt;, but the two of them work hand in hand. Content is the information that is being communicated, and presentation is how it is displayed. A recent example of this is found within Apple&amp;rsquo;s new &lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.com/@GuillemBruix/design-your-dark-and-tinted-versions-of-your-app-icon-for-ios-18-827444a31851&#34;&gt;ios 18&lt;/a&gt; where users can now use a dark mode on their home screens. This new feature alters the look of your apps and home screen, but all of the data and information you are seeing is the same.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation_adhikari_sayana</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_adhikari_sayana/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 19:51:12 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_adhikari_sayana/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Presentation?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Presentation is the general concept and processes around modifying content for display in a particular channel, usually through templating. A template applied to content will result in output which is then delivered. (Deane Barker, Web Content Management glossary)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In my words&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Presentation refers to how information is displayed or shown. It&amp;rsquo;s about the look of the content, such as the layout, fonts, colors, and style. It determines how users see and interact with the material, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t change the actual content itself.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation_Myers_Albert</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_myers_albert/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 12:47:55 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_myers_albert/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-presentation&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Presentation&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Content is the raw data, while presentation is how it&amp;rsquo;s shown&amp;rdquo; (Mauricio Harp).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;presentation-in-my-own-words&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Presentation in my own words&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Good preseentation can make the content you want to produce stand out among other version of similar content. It also needs to be aimed toward the consumer not just the people producing the content&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;presentation-in-canvas&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Presentation in Canvas&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://uk.instructure.com/?login_success=1&#34;&gt;Canvas&lt;/a&gt; has a great presentation as it is aimed toward college students. Most college students do not want to work to hard to access cerrtain assignments or readings for classes. As soon as you login into Canavs you can change the way your main page looks by either Card view, List view, and Recent activity. This gives a way for the consumer to customize their own version of the site. Then on the left side are different tabs that can take you were you want to go.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation - Omari</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_chaplin_omari/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_chaplin_omari/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Presentation&lt;/strong&gt; is specificaly the the visual elements of a piece of content that are displayed on devices and other channels to provide a specific experience for the user, according to &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/computer-science/presentation-content#:~:text=Presentation%20content%20refers%20to%20the,provide%20a%20consistent%20user%20experience.&#34;&gt;Barker&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To me, I find presentation to be the aspect that you want the user to actually see, and usually removing itself from the code and back end as much as possible&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One example of presentation is on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.uky.edu/&#34;&gt;UK&amp;rsquo;s website&lt;/a&gt;. What we see here is &lt;strong&gt;the actual content of the page&lt;/strong&gt; presented in a way that looks cohesive and visually appealing! Inspecting the page with right-click or F12 shows a whole host of information and code, but the user (without effort) will not see this.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation (Ahmad)</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_amjad_ahmad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_amjad_ahmad/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;“The general concept and processes around modifying content for display in a particular channel, usually through templating. A template applied to content will result in output which is then delivered.” (Barker, 2013).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You could say it&amp;rsquo;s the aesthetic of something, like how someone shows themselves to others by how they dress, theie maneruisms, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://store.kde.org/browse?cat=104&amp;amp;ord=latest&#34;&gt;KDE Themes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll use Linux (KDE to be exact) as an example, as you&amp;rsquo;re given different themes and one of them can change the general look of the desktop which can affect things like spacing&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation_mccoy_hayes</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_mccoy_hayes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 17:44:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_mccoy_hayes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The general concept and processes around modifying content for display in a particular channel, usually through templating. A template applied to content will result in output which is then delivered.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Deane Barker, Web Content Management glossary&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-presentation-to-me&#34;&gt;What is Presentation To Me?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To me, presentation is how content is displayed. It is what you see when you go&#xA;to a webpage or an application, and it is anything with a graphical user interface.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Content Aggregation&#34; - Omari</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_chaplin_omari/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 10:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_chaplin_omari/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-content-aggregation&#34;&gt;What is &amp;ldquo;content aggregation&amp;rdquo;?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;According to the slides and &lt;em&gt;Deane Barker&lt;/em&gt;, content aggregation is a purposeful grouping of content for the purposes of organization or presentation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Personally, I would describe content aggregation as using specific classifying aspects of content, and using them to group similar things together.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;an-example&#34;&gt;An Example&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When I think of content aggregation, I think about Reddit! One of my favorite subreddits aggregates specific flairs, and each post that falls under it is organized under them. As you can see in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reddit.com/r/LiminalSpace/?f=flair_name%3A%22Video%20Game%22&#34;&gt;Liminal Spaces Subreddit&lt;/a&gt;, I linked to the flairs that specified &amp;ldquo;Video Games&amp;rdquo;. Therefore, I can find posts easily that match that description!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation_donnelly_matthew</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_donnelly_matthew/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 13:24:37 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_donnelly_matthew/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;defining-presentation&#34;&gt;Defining Presentation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Dean Barker gave a great definition of presentation, he said that presentation is, &amp;ldquo;The general concept and processes around modifying content for display in a particular channel, usually through templating. A template applied to content will result in output which is then delivered.&amp;rdquo; (Barker, 2013).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;in-my-own-words&#34;&gt;In my own &lt;em&gt;words&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Presentation is how you view something in it&amp;rsquo;s simpliest form. It is how you see a website, and how easiliy or hard you can navigate through it. Considering what kind of presentation is best for your audiance is extremely important, as it could either make quality of life better or frustrating for users to naviagte and view.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_Ilunga_Victoire</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_ilunga_victoire/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 11:01:18 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_ilunga_victoire/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;understanding-content-aggregation&#34;&gt;Understanding Content Aggregation&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;definition-of-content-aggregation&#34;&gt;Definition of Content Aggregation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Content aggregation refers to the process of collecting information or content from multiple sources and presenting it in a consolidated format for users to consume. According to Deane Barker&amp;rsquo;s book &lt;em&gt;Web Content Management: systems, features, and best practices&lt;/em&gt;, &amp;ldquo;content aggregation involves gathering content from external or internal sources, organizing it, and displaying it in a coherent way that adds value for the user.&amp;rdquo; (Barker, 2016).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_Ilunga_Victoire 2</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_ilunga_victoire2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 11:01:18 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_ilunga_victoire2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;understanding-content-aggregations&#34;&gt;Understanding Content Aggregations&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;definition-of-content-aggregation&#34;&gt;Definition of Content Aggregation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Content aggregation refers to the process of collecting information or content from multiple sources and presenting it in a consolidated format for users to consume. According to Deane Barker&amp;rsquo;s book &lt;em&gt;Web Content Management: systems, features, and best practices&lt;/em&gt;, &amp;ldquo;content aggregation involves gathering content from external or internal sources, organizing it, and displaying it in a coherent way that adds value for the user.&amp;rdquo; (Barker, 2016).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ilunga Victoire Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ilunga-victoire-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 10:56:37 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ilunga-victoire-post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>presentation_bryant_henry</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_bryant_henry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 10:52:17 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_bryant_henry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-presentation&#34;&gt;What is Presentation?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In &lt;em&gt;Examining the Separation Between Presentation and Content&lt;/em&gt;, author Deane Barker defines presentation as &amp;ldquo;the use of colors, fonts, etc.&amp;rdquo; on a website that changes the way the content looks (Barker, 2013).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In other words, this means that presentation is the way that the content looks when a user visits a website. The presentation can include the font that the content is set in, the size of the font, the color of the background, and many other general visual attributes of the website. From my own personal experience, I know that the content can even be changed by the user. In short, presentation is just how the website looks to the visitor.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation_chen_ricky</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_chen_ricky/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 10:51:28 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_chen_ricky/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-presentation&#34;&gt;What is Presentation?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;According to Deane Barker, &amp;ldquo;Content from its aesthetic surrounding, so the &amp;lsquo;presentation&amp;rsquo; is the use of colors, fonts, etc.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Barker, D.(2016). &lt;a href=&#34;https://deanebarker.net/tech/glossary/presentation/&#34;&gt;Presentation&lt;/a&gt;. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;to-my-understanding&#34;&gt;To my Understanding&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Presentation is how content is show. Regardless how presentation has changed, the content will still be the same.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;example&#34;&gt;Example&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An example of presentation is themes for Shopify. Here is an example -&amp;gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://themes.shopify.com/themes&#34;&gt;Shopify Theme&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is example of presentation. Shopify is a platform that lets entrepreneur sell things online. In Shopify user can change the theme easily while keeping their content the same. Keeping what they&amp;rsquo;re selling still in the website. There is more than just themes to change, user can change how they want to show their products, changing colors, and etc. All for a better experince for the consumer, different themes can boost sales.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>presentation_nguyen_nhi</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_nguyen_nhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 10:26:39 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_nguyen_nhi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;presentation&#34;&gt;Presentation&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The definition of this concept is &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Content from its aesthetic surroundings, so the &amp;lsquo;presentation&amp;rsquo; is the use of colors, fonts, etc.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; (Barker, 2016)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In other words, the explanation for this concept is &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;The presentation refers to how content is visually framed and displayed but the content remains the same.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;example&#34;&gt;Example&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One example I use is &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.instagram.com&#34;&gt;Instagram’s dark mode&lt;/a&gt;. Instagram allows users to change between a light mode and a dark mode, where the background switches to black, and fonts and icons adjust to maintain visibility.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_lewis_grant</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_lewis_grant/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 05:36:19 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_lewis_grant/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Content aggregation is &amp;ldquo;An intentional grouping of content for the purposes of organization or presentation&amp;rdquo; Deane Barker, Web Content Management glossary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This means to me what tools or ways we can organize information, such as adding tags to files, dates, or names. A real-life case of this is when I use Lightroom for photography. Lightroom allows the user to organize their photos by metadata and other methods, such as keywords, ratings, titles that can be created, and folders to separate groups of folders. This is executing intentional grouping of content. As for some of my trips, I purposefully group them in a file and can then sort by my rating, date, and location where I took the photos. You can get nit-picky in which you want to organize the images.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_mason_avery</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_mason_avery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 21:46:43 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_mason_avery/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What is Content Aggregation?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;An intentional grouping of content for the purposes of organization or presentation&amp;rdquo; Barker, D. (2016). Web Content Management. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I immediately think to myself that content aggregation is more like content presentation. It&amp;rsquo;s the presentation of what the content is, how its organized, what links to it? How is it portrayed to an audience. How does the user see the content?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The example I have for content aggregation would be something like an individuals youtube feed. Youtube will organize other content based of your subscriptions, watched, liked or disliked videos. Thus presenting you with options they believe you may like.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_donnelly_matthew</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_donnelly_matthew/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 21:34:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_donnelly_matthew/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;defining-content-aggregation&#34;&gt;Defining &amp;ldquo;Content Aggregation&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In Deane Barker&amp;rsquo;s words, content aggregation is, &amp;ldquo;An intentional grouping of content for the purposes of organization or presentation&amp;rdquo; (Barker).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;in-my-own-words&#34;&gt;In my own words&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would say that it really just makes it easier to find specific things on websites, since it uses grouping and organization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;examples&#34;&gt;Examples?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First thing that comes to mind is Reddit. Reddit&amp;rsquo;s home page is super simple and is easy to navigate for new users, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reddit.com/&#34;&gt;Reddit Home Page&lt;/a&gt; . If you are using reddit on the computer, on the left side there are topics that you can browse through. If you are interested in movies/tv you can just click on this topic ( which is a great example of content aggregation ).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defining Content Aggregation</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_livingston_chauncey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 21:16:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_livingston_chauncey/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-content-aggregation&#34;&gt;What is Content Aggregation?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To me, content aggregation is simple; it&amp;rsquo;s just the organization of content. Deane Barker -someone who knows a lot more than me- describes it as&#xA;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;An intentional grouping of content for organization or presentation.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;A straightforward definition, but content aggregation can get somewhat complex.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-is-it-used&#34;&gt;How is it used?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the more common examples of content aggregation is organizing things into categories or using tags. On platforms like Instagram, people can add hashtags that go with their posts to add them to other libraries of similar content. Not only does this help the person posting, but it makes it easier for people to find related information. A great example of this is&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pinterest.com/&#34;&gt;Pintrest&lt;/a&gt; where almost all of the content is separated by tags and can be organized in hundreds of categories.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_Hotko_AJ</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_hotko_aj/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 21:07:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_hotko_aj/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;content-aggregation-defined&#34;&gt;Content Aggregation Defined&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“an intentional grouping of content for the purposes of organizations or presentation” (Barker, 2016).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-interpretation-of-content-aggregation&#34;&gt;My Interpretation of Content Aggregation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My interpretation of content aggregation is that It organizes content in a logical manner in which it is easier to consume&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;example-of-content-aggregation---instagram&#34;&gt;Example of Content Aggregation - Instagram&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A user can easily see content from creators in that they are following simply just by scrolling. On the bottom the screen the user has the options to make a post of their own, search for specific content, access an area in which they can see content posted by anyone even if they are not following them, and view their own profile. This style of content aggregation has everything organized in such a way that makes it very easy for the user to navigate.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_harp_mauricio</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_harp_mauricio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 16:08:32 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_harp_mauricio/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;concept-in-your-own-words-content-aggregation-gathers-and-organizes-different-information-into-a-single-space&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Definition&lt;/strong&gt;: Content aggregation intentionally groups content for organization or presentation&amp;quot; (Barker, 2024).&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;Concept in Your Own Words&lt;/strong&gt;: Content aggregation gathers and organizes different information into a single space.&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Real-Life Example - YouTube playlists let users group related videos.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How it shows Content Aggregation - It shows similar videos in one place and makes it easier for users to watch or search for them without searching for each video&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_Myers_Albert</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_myers_albert/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 12:13:27 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_myers_albert/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-content-aggregation&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Content aggregation&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Content agreegation is, &amp;ldquo;An intentional grouping of content for the purposes of organization or presentation&amp;rdquo; (Deane Barker).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;content-aggregation-in-my-own-words&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Content aggregation in my own words&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Makes it easier to find specific content on the sites UI.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;content-aggregation-on-tiktok&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Content aggregation on TikTok&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Tiktok for instance has a for you page (FYP) section and a following section. This gives the user the freedom to choose between fresh content from someone they don&amp;rsquo;t follow or to watch new relased content from someone they follow. This seperates the content by a specific group and makes it easier for a user to navigate.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Define content aggregation (Ahmad)</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_amjad_ahmad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 09:59:49 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_amjad_ahmad/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;“An intentional grouping of content for the purposes of organization or presentation” Barker, D. (2016). Web Content Management. O’Reilly Media&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Essentialy the execution of how you show content (Ex. Formatting)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Forums &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Internet_forum&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A forum is usually formatted into main pages (Normally on the top) and when you click one, will show a list of sub forums / pages to make it easy to browse&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Take GameFAQs for example&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[hi] (&lt;a href=&#34;https://gamefaqs.gamespot.com/&#34;&gt;https://gamefaqs.gamespot.com/&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_mccoy_hayes</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_mccoy_hayes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 17:44:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_mccoy_hayes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;An intentional grouping of content for the purposes of organization or presentation&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Deane Barker, Web Content Management glossary&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-content-aggregation-to-me&#34;&gt;What is Content Aggregation To Me?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Content aggregation is how content is organized or laid out so that it can be&#xA;viewed and navigated by users.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;examples&#34;&gt;Examples?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An example that comes to mind for me is BuzzFeed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here is the link to their site: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.buzzfeed.com/&#34;&gt;https://www.buzzfeed.com/&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I used to spend a decent amount of time scrolling through their site&#xA;to find fun quizzes and articles, and how they categorize their website made&#xA;it easy to find a lot of different content related to things I was looking for.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation_coleman_bryan</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_coleman_bryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 10:05:25 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_coleman_bryan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Presentation&lt;/strong&gt; refers to the visual elements of a piece of content that are displayed on various medias and devices to provide a specific experience for the user. The source for my definition can be found &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/computer-science/presentation-content#:~:text=Presentation%20content%20refers%20to%20the,provide%20a%20consistent%20user%20experience.&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&#xA;In my own words, presentation refers to the various aspects designed to help display content to the user. This can be achieved through both visual and information elements.&#xA;One example of this concept of presentation is a YouTube video by Bryson DeChambeau. Within the video we see this concept of presentation as he make sure his voice is heard clearly through the use of microphones, and he makes sure there is good lighting and the recording looks good, so that the video is good quality, well perceived, and attractive to the audience. Lastly, he also tracks the golf balls he hits with a red line so the audience can see and better follow along. These aspects all help lead to a good presentation factor in his videos. The source for my example can be found &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YUnIuodiOV4&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_adhikari_sayana</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_adhikari_sayana/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 19:36:25 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_adhikari_sayana/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is &amp;lsquo;content aggregation&amp;rsquo;?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An intentional grouping of content for the purposes of organization or presentation. (Dean Barker, Web Content Management Glossary)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In my own words&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Content aggregation means gathering information from different places and putting it all together in one spot. It helps people find everything they need, like news or articles, without going to many different websites.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Example&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Example of content aggregation is YouTube. YouTube aggregates videos from countless creators and channels, allowing users to discover and watch a wide variety of content in one platform.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGC_Ilunga_victoire</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_ilunga_victoire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 23:09:07 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_ilunga_victoire/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;definition-of-user-generated-content&#34;&gt;Definition of User-Generated Content&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would define User-generated content as content made by regular users or customers that is usually shared on social media or other platforms. According to the article &amp;ldquo;A Straightforward Approach to User Generated Content that Connects,&amp;rdquo; user content is is original, brand-specific content created by customers (at no cost to you) and published on social media or other channels (Oladipo, 2022).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Example&lt;/strong&gt;: A popular platform where UGC thrives is Instagram. Users create and post photos or videos, share stories, and engage with others through comments and likes. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.instagram.com/&#34;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGC_Hotko_AJ</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_hotko_aj/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 15:39:43 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_hotko_aj/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;User generated content defined by Deane Barker as “Content generated by non-editors, usually from the public side of the website.” (Barker, 2016). My understanding of this definition is that user generated content is anything that someone who is using a website or app as it is intended to be used. An example of this would be reviews that are left on a restaurant’s yelp page. People (non-editors) use the app to generate their content which is a review of the restaurant. Here is a yelp page for an &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.yelp.com/biz/pasta-garage-italian-cafe-lexington-2&#34;&gt;example&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGC_adhikari_sayana</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_adhikari_sayana/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 14:23:32 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_adhikari_sayana/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is UGC?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;User-generated content (UGC) is published information that an unpaid contributor provides to a website. The information might be a photo, video, blog or discussion forum post, poll response or comment made through a social media website (Kinza Yasar, 2022). UGC can include:&#xA;Text,Photos,Videos,Audio,Reviews,Podcasts,Blog posts,Testimonials,Software, like video game mods.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In my own words&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;UGC stands for User-Generated Content. It includes photos, videos, post that are created by regular people post and not the companies on social media.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content_adhikari_sayana</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_adhikari_sayana/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 14:03:34 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_adhikari_sayana/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Whai is Content?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Content is a type of information that is made to engage, inform, or entertain the audience. Content can be in various formats such as text, images, videos, audio and any type of interactive elements.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In my own words&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In my opinion content is something that we consume through digital platform. Watching some content and consuming entertainment plus some valuable information is a plus point cause you are not wasting your time but doing something mindful.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>content_Ilunga_Victoire.md</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_ilunga_victoire_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 10:19:24 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_ilunga_victoire_post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;defining-content&#34;&gt;Defining Content&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Content&lt;/strong&gt; refers to information or experiences meant to inform or engage an audience (author: Merriam Webster dictionnary).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In simpler terms, content is anything shared with others to communicate, be it a blog post, social media update, video, or podcast.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;example-of-content&#34;&gt;Example of Content&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One example of content I consume is &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.uky.edu/canvas/&#34;&gt;Canvas&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizing Content Grant</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_lewis_grant/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 15:23:23 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_lewis_grant/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;##User Generated Content&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the past week, we have discussed user-generated content and its meaning. User-generated content or media created by a human. In the Podcast Episode: Wordle and the Web We Need a Podcast on EFF, the hosts talk about the meaning and what they feel by it. One of the hosts says it was crazy that people now refer to media or art, such as music, as content and sometimes not as its correct form, even when it comes from the heart.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGC_harp_mauricio</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_harp_mauricio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 15:23:23 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_harp_mauricio/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Definition of UGC&#xA;User-generated content refers to &amp;ldquo;content generated by non-editors, usually from the public side of the website&amp;rdquo; (Source: user-generated content and CMS extensions slide 14, Week 3).&#xA;In my own words&#xA;I think UGC is content made by everyday users, like posts and reviews shared on platforms.&#xA;Real-life Example: Reddit&#xA;Reddit is a prime example of UGC. Users submit posts, links, and discussions across different communities. For instance, in&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/?rdt=44277&#34;&gt;r/technology&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;, users can share and discuss tech news, showing how the platform relies on user-generated content.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content_harp_mauricio</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_harp_mauricio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:58:35 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_harp_mauricio/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Definition of Content:&#xA;Content is information created through a report for humans to see through publication. It is organized and tailored to convey a message, provide entertainment, or share knowledge (Source: Slide 3, Week 2 Lecture, &amp;ldquo;slides on content, content, and mission, and content models&amp;rdquo;).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In My Own Words:&#xA;I think content is any information that someone produces and refines to share with others. It’s engaging or informative, often reflecting the creator&amp;rsquo;s perspective.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>aggregation_bryant_henry</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_bryant_henry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:53:07 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_bryant_henry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-content-aggregation&#34;&gt;What is Content Aggregation?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In &lt;em&gt;Web Content Management&lt;/em&gt;, author Deane Barker defines content aggregation as &amp;ldquo;an intentional grouping of content for purposes of organization or presentation&amp;rdquo; (Barker, 2016).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In other words, this means that content aggregation is the way that content is displayed on a website in order for users to view said content via either the organization of the website or the terms that the user chooses to see. Content aggregation is simply the way that the content is displayed with other content on websites. This content can be grouped by the website administrator for purposes of organization or navigtion, or it can be returned by users who filter content through various built-in organizational methods on a site, such as running a search for specific things on a website, or using tags to filter.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_chen_ricky</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_chen_ricky/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:51:44 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_chen_ricky/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-content-aggregation&#34;&gt;What is Content Aggregation?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;According to Deane Barker, &amp;ldquo;An intentional grouping of content for the purposes of organization or presentation.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Barker, D.(2016). &lt;a href=&#34;https://deanebarker.net/books/squirrel/content-aggregation/&#34;&gt;Web Content Management&lt;/a&gt;. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;to-my-understanding&#34;&gt;To my Understanding&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Content Aggregation is a specific way to organize content to show to the public.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;example&#34;&gt;Example&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An example of content aggregation is news pages. Here is an example -&amp;gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://news.google.com/home?hl=en-US&amp;amp;gl=US&amp;amp;ceid=US:en&#34;&gt;Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is example of content aggregation. Currently the page is the same for evveryone, in the public. It also has a &amp;ldquo;For you&amp;rdquo; section where if user visit Google News frequently and brower through their interest of news, Google News will generate more topics in the &amp;ldquo;For you&amp;rdquo; section so the users can stay in their website for longer. They organized their content for specific interest to the user to present to the public.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>aggregation_nguyen_nhi</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_nguyen_nhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:26:39 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_nguyen_nhi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;user-generated-content&#34;&gt;User-generated Content&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The definition of this concept is &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;An intentional grouping of content for purposes of organization or presentation.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; (Barker, 2016)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Deane Barker, Web Content Management glossary&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In other words, the explanation for this concept is &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;The content aggregation gathers content based on certain criteria, such as a topic or keyword, making it easier for users to discover relevant content without manually searching for it.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;example&#34;&gt;Example&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One example I use is &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pinterest.com&#34;&gt;Pintrest&lt;/a&gt;. if I&amp;rsquo;m looking for design inspiration, Pinterest aggregates relevant content such as blog posts, portfolio images, and design ideas—from various sources and allows me to &amp;ldquo;pin&amp;rdquo; them to a virtual board.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is **User-Generated Content**? - Omari</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_chaplin_omari/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 04:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_chaplin_omari/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-user-generated-content&#34;&gt;What is User-Generated Content?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;According to the slides and &lt;em&gt;Deane Barker&lt;/em&gt;, user-generated content is content generated by non-editors, and usually from the public side of the website.&#xA;An example of user-generated content would be a simple Instagram post of a selfie. The user generated and posted it with the intention for people to see.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;an-example&#34;&gt;An Example&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One example of &lt;em&gt;user-generated content&lt;/em&gt; in action is &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pQQ8OXnklrY&amp;amp;pp=ygUGY2xhaXJl&#34;&gt;another awesome video&lt;/a&gt; by Claire Saffitz.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGC_myers_albert</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_myers_albert/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 00:27:04 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_myers_albert/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-user-generated-content&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;user-generated content&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;User-generated content (UGC) is published information that an unpaid contributor provides to a website&amp;rdquo; (Yasar, 2022). Somebody puts out photo or video into the public domain that anhyone can use.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Social media posts are great examples of UGC. One video can be circulated to potentially multiple different accounts that then give the original person credit for the use of their post. These posts can give someone a potential platform to use.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGC_donnelly_matthew</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_donnelly_matthew/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:18:45 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_donnelly_matthew/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;defining-user-generated-content&#34;&gt;Defining &amp;ldquo;user generated content&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;User generated content is typically &amp;ldquo;generated by non-editors, usually from the public side of the website&amp;rdquo; (Barker). UCG is extremely broad, really anything that anybody posts/replies to can be considered for this; however, to me I would say that it is content created by users, for others to view.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;examples-of-ucg&#34;&gt;Examples of UCG&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reddit.com/r/photography/comments/2l9z1y/setting_up_a_home_darkroom_difficult/&#34;&gt;Reddit Post&lt;/a&gt; This is a simple example of UCG. Even though this post is about 10 years old, this user was asking questions on how to set up a darkroom. I use reddit all of the time if I need inspiration or just have any questions. But there are many other websites that you can find UCG on.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hayes McCoy: User-Generated Content</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_mccoy_hayes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 20:05:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_mccoy_hayes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Content generated by non-editors, usually from the public side of the website.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Deane Barker, Web Content Management glossary&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-user-generated-content-to-me&#34;&gt;What is User-Generated Content to Me?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To me, user-generated content is content that is published on a website by users of&#xA;the website.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-an-example-of-this&#34;&gt;What is an Example of This?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The first example that comes to my mind when I hear user-generated content&#xA;is Wikipedia. Here is the link to their website: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wikipedia.org/&#34;&gt;https://www.wikipedia.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is even quoted on their website:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGC_mason_avery</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_mason_avery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:36:09 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_mason_avery/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;user-generated-content&#34;&gt;User generated content&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Content generated by non-editors, usually from the public side of the website&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Barker, D. (n.d.). &lt;em&gt;User-generated content&lt;/em&gt;. Deane Barker. &lt;a href=&#34;https://deanebarker.net/tech/glossary/user-generated-content/&#34;&gt;https://deanebarker.net/tech/glossary/user-generated-content/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To me User generated content are things in which users of a particular platform post/create.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sources of content I regularly consume are that of Twitter, Reddit and various internet forums. In these platforms users are creating posts and actively contributing to discussions and or creating content themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;ex&#34;&gt;Ex:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reddit.com/&#34;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defining User-Generated Content</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_livingston_chauncey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:33:21 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_livingston_chauncey/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-even-is-user-generated-content&#34;&gt;What Even Is User-Generated Content?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When speaking about content on the Internet, it is almost impossible not to mention user-generated content. There are millions of new pieces of content on the internet every day, and they don&amp;rsquo;t just appear out of thin air, they are fueled&#x9;by people like me and you. UGC was referred to as&#xA;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Content generated by non-editors, usually from the public side of the website&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;by Deane Barker. To me, UGC is simply just content created by users for different platforms.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Define user generated content (Ahmad)</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_amjad_ahmad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 09:59:49 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_amjad_ahmad/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;User-generated content (UGC) is published information that an unpaid contributor provides to a website. The information might be a photo, video, blog or discussion forum post, poll response or comment made through a social media website. (TechTarget)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Content by the general public and not those like corporations, moderators, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Internet_forum&#34;&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Internet_forum&lt;/a&gt; They&amp;rsquo;re message bpards&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Forums are an example, where users make posts in sub forums while mods or admin make posts in the home page.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_coleman_bryan</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_coleman_bryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 12:37:01 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_coleman_bryan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Content aggregation can be defined as the process of collecting and showcasing related content from a plethora of sources in one singular place. I got this definition from &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.indeed.com/career-advice/career-development/content-aggregation&#34;&gt;this website.&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;In my own words, content aggregation is the topic of gathering and collecting content, information, or data for the user from outside sources and displaying it all together on a singular website or platform.&#xA;A great example of this topic is Google News. Google News acts as an example of content aggregation because it collects and organizes information from various sources but displays it on Google News. &lt;a href=&#34;https://news.google.com/home?hl=en-US&amp;amp;gl=US&amp;amp;ceid=US:en&#34;&gt;Here is the link to Google News.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGC_coleman_bryan</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_coleman_bryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 10:28:17 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_coleman_bryan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User-generated content&lt;/strong&gt; is content generated by non-editors, usually from the public side of the website. I got this definition from the class sides, which can be found &lt;a href=&#34;https://spencergreenhalgh.com/_302_2024_w3_c1.html#14&#34;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;In my own words, user-generated content is any published type of information or media where a contributor or user provides that information as opposed to an editor.&#xA;One example I have for user-generated content is that I always read or look at customer reviews before I purchase anything online, such as from Amazon. I have included a link for a game, and at the bottom there are customer reviews from those who have spent time and money on that game, so they are always a genuine experience and reaction. They serve as user-generated content as the reviews are not posted from editors, but random users on the site with the product.&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/Madden-NFL-25-Xbox-X/dp/B0D3P4HV27/ref=asc_df_B0D3P4HV27/?tag=hyprod-20&amp;amp;linkCode=df0&amp;amp;hvadid=692875362841&amp;amp;hvpos=&amp;amp;hvnetw=g&amp;amp;hvrand=10801584644197785728&amp;amp;hvpone=&amp;amp;hvptwo=&amp;amp;hvqmt=&amp;amp;hvdev=c&amp;amp;hvdvcmdl=&amp;amp;hvlocint=&amp;amp;hvlocphy=9014318&amp;amp;hvtargid=pla-2281435179018&amp;amp;mcid=a6d91713b6643d728a5d3818896c8d86&amp;amp;hvocijid=10801584644197785728-B0D3P4HV27-&amp;amp;hvexpln=73&amp;amp;th=1&#34;&gt;Here is my link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGC_nguyen_nhi</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_nguyen_nhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 10:26:39 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_nguyen_nhi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;user-generated-content&#34;&gt;User-generated Content&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The definition of this concept is &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Content generated by non-editors, usually from the public side of the website.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Deane Barker, Web Content Management glossary&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In other words, the explanation for this concept is &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;User-generated content are the contents that are created and shared by users. This can include social media posts, blog articles, product reviews, and more.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;example&#34;&gt;Example&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/EoZYbFykJAI?si=29KSOQB-yur1p2rz&#34;&gt;NikkieTutorials YouTube&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;NikkieTutorials is a popular beauty YouTuber who creates and shares makeup tutorials, product reviews, and other beauty-related content. This is an example for user-generated content because she is an individual creator sharing her expertise and passion with her audience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGC_bryant_henry</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_bryant_henry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 10:24:07 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_bryant_henry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-user-generated-content&#34;&gt;What is User-Generated Content?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In &lt;em&gt;Web Content Management&lt;/em&gt;, author Deane Barker defines user-generated content as content (see last post for definition) that was &amp;ldquo;generated by non-editors, usually from the public side of the website&amp;rdquo; (Barker, 2016).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In other words, this means that user-generated content is something that someone who visits or uses a website uploads to the website for other users to view and interact with, without going into the backend of the website to edit the raw code powering it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGC_chen_ricky</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_chen_ricky/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 10:23:27 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_chen_ricky/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-user-generated-content&#34;&gt;What is User-Generated Content?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;According to Deane Barker, &amp;ldquo;Content generated by non-editors, usually from the public side of the website.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Barker, D.(2016). &lt;a href=&#34;https://deanebarker.net/tech/glossary/user-generated-content/&#34;&gt;Web Content Management&lt;/a&gt;. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;to-my-understanding&#34;&gt;To my Understanding&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;User generated content is something that is created by non professionals and usually shows the real/raw identity of something without getting paid.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;example&#34;&gt;Example&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An example of user generated content is reviews for a Amazon product. Here is an example -&amp;gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/gp/customer-reviews/R3T29DPZDMA2FX/ref=cm_cr_getr_d_rvw_ttl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ASIN=B0BQ37B73B&#34;&gt;Amazon Review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content definition by Ben</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_parsons_ben/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 10:16:12 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_parsons_ben/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;According to Dr. Barker, &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Content is information produced through editorial process and ultimately intended for human consumption via publication.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt; Barker, D. (2016). Web Content Management. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For me, I believe that content is &lt;strong&gt;something that is meant to entertain other people, inform people, and or help people. It is also something that is created by humans for humans.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An example of a piece of content is a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PXaLc9AYIcg&amp;amp;ab_channel=TechSource&#34;&gt;how to youtube video&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;This ties to my definition because this video is a video that is made by a person for someone to learn something new.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content_kemper_lea</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_kemper_lea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 10:11:20 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_kemper_lea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-content&#34;&gt;What is Content?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Content&lt;/strong&gt; is created in an editorial process and designed for human consumption. In the editorial process, content is often influenced by the creators&amp;rsquo; vision, voice, and guidelines of the platform or organization, in order to convey a certain message. I post content for the Tattoo parlor I work for. I use Instagram, Facebook, and our website to distribute pictures, videos, and announcements. To keep up to date with trends I regularly consume content from other tattoo artist posts. As a consumer of this content, I can shift my perspective and become a better editor for my shop page. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=61560055360761&#34;&gt;Shop Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is **Content**? - Omari</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_chaplin_omari/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 04:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_chaplin_omari/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-content&#34;&gt;What is Content?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;According to the slides and &lt;em&gt;Deane Barker&lt;/em&gt;, content is created by editorial process and intended for consumption by a human audience.&#xA;To me, content is anything we humans create and put onto the internet. Anything from blogposts, to videos, to music, to images: all of it is content!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;an-example&#34;&gt;An Example&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One example of &lt;em&gt;content&lt;/em&gt; in action is &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JlzmsTiOJnU&amp;amp;pp=ygUdY2xhaXJlIHNhZmZpdHogY2lubmFtb24gcm9sbHM%3D&#34;&gt;this awesome video&lt;/a&gt; by Claire Saffitz. In this video, she demonstrates one of her recipes from her book. This content is &lt;strong&gt;created by her&lt;/strong&gt; and is &lt;strong&gt;intended for us to consume&lt;/strong&gt;. In this instance, it is meant to entertain and inform us about cooking!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaplin First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/chaplin-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 23:43:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/chaplin-first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m &lt;strong&gt;Omari&lt;/strong&gt; and this is my &lt;em&gt;first&lt;/em&gt; post! My favorite website is &lt;a href=&#34;https://google.com/&#34;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content Livingston Chauncey</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_livingston_chauncey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 23:06:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_livingston_chauncey/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-content&#34;&gt;What is Content?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Formally &amp;ldquo;Content is information produced through editorial process and ultimately intended for human consumption via publication.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;Barker, D. (2016). Web Content Management. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;In my opinion content is various types of information or media shared on any type of platform. For example &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.google.com/imgres?q=camaro%20zl1&amp;amp;imgurl=https%3A%2F%2Fhips.hearstapps.com%2Fhmg-prod%2Fimages%2F2024-chevrolet-camaro-zl1-collectors-edition-647e05de95705.jpg&amp;amp;imgrefurl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.caranddriver.com%2Fchevrolet%2Fcamaro-zl1&amp;amp;docid=tgcg5TloakjEwM&amp;amp;tbnid=sQ-ppBFeGNAQJM&amp;amp;vet=12ahUKEwiPzLHJtLeIAxXHrYkEHeUEB8MQM3oECBoQAA..i&amp;amp;w=5000&amp;amp;h=3329&amp;amp;hcb=2&amp;amp;ved=2ahUKEwiPzLHJtLeIAxXHrYkEHeUEB8MQM3oECBoQAA&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; is a website that has multiple types of content including an article and pictures.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content Rael Kapanga</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content-rael-kapanga/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 20:08:06 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content-rael-kapanga/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-is-content&#34;&gt;what is content:&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Dash discusses the term &amp;ldquo;user-generated content&amp;rdquo; and how many of the people who create this content feel that the phrase doesn&amp;rsquo;t accurately represent them. He also notes that many younger individuals today prefer to call themselves &amp;ldquo;content creators&amp;rdquo; instead. (Richman, 2022)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;in my own term, content is  refers to any information or material that is created, shared, and consumed through various forms of media. It can include text, images, videos, audio, or a combination of these elements, and is used to inform, entertain, engage, or educate an audience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lastname First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/lastname-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 20:06:23 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/lastname-first-post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content_mason_avery</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_mason_avery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 16:26:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_mason_avery/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;“Content is information produced through editorial process and ultimately intended for human consumption via publication.” Barker, D. (2016). Web Content Management. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I understand this concept as the creation of something with humans as the consumers. Videos, movies, podcasts, interviews, books and journals are some examples. Authors write books with the hopes that someone consumes them, i.e. reads their work. A chef creates a dish that he hopes customers will enjoy etc.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kapanga First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/kapanga-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 11:23:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/kapanga-first-post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kapanga Rael Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/kapanga-rael-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 11:22:35 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/kapanga-rael-post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>content_donnelly_matthew</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_donnelly_matthew/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 11:17:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_donnelly_matthew/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-content&#34;&gt;What is Content?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Definition of Content&amp;rdquo;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;Content&lt;/strong&gt; would be something that users create and is &amp;ldquo;intended for consumption by a human audience&amp;rdquo; (Barker, 2016)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My Definition&lt;/strong&gt; would be technically anything can be content; however, it needs to have that editorial process and needs to be consumed by humans in the simplest of terms.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Content&lt;/strong&gt; that I regularly &lt;em&gt;consume&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If I ever feel like some of my photos are lacking any substance, I usually check out this website &lt;a href=&#34;https://eyecannndy.com/&#34;&gt;my link&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;The reason that this website is &lt;strong&gt;content&lt;/strong&gt; is that this is made for a human audiences, for creatives that are looking to find inspiration or try and recreate a visual shot.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementation Proposal</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_donnelly_matthew/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 11:17:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_donnelly_matthew/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;workflow-implementation&#34;&gt;Workflow implementation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The very first step that we should take is communicating on teams. Brainstorm on their and publish our ideas. Taking our brainstorm to the next step then implenting them into wordpress. After this, edits will be done to make sure that this process goes by smoothly. After everything is approved, we can finally ad the finishing touches then publish them to the website.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;class-expectations&#34;&gt;Class expectations&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think that people should work on all roles; however, if people are not comfortable enough about working directly with wordpress, then they should focus on other tasks. People that are comfortable working on the backend and frontend should have a seperate chat to discuss the easiest ways of doing things so the website itself doesn&amp;rsquo;t get complicated. I think that the way we setup and discussed in class will work perfectly for us in the coming months.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow Implementation Proposition- Omari</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_chaplin_omari/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 11:17:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_chaplin_omari/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;lets-make-a-plan&#34;&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s Make a Plan!&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We need to think about how our workflow will go&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have a few technologies available to us that we can use to implement and execute our workflow in WordPress, Teams, e-mail, Canvas, and any other technologies we bring into consideration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;we-can-use-these-tools-to&#34;&gt;We can use these tools to:&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Communicate with each other (text or voice)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Set deadlines and due dates on calendars&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Share data and progress&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Screenshare&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Setup and attend group meetings&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Test and preview ideas&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;reasonable-expectations&#34;&gt;Reasonable Expectations&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We should expect each other to use these technologies for the reasons listed above and more in order to get our work done efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content class blog</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_kirkpatrick_sam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_kirkpatrick_sam/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;2&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;definition&#34;&gt;Definition&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Definition: Data, digital code, images, graphics, sounds, text or any other similar material regardless of the method or medium of communication of such content or the purpose of the communication. Source: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.lawinsider.com/dictionary/media-content#:~:text=Copy-,Media%20Content%20means%20data%2C%20digital%20code%2C%20images%2C%20graphics%2C,the%20purpose%20of%20the%20communication&#34;&gt;https://www.lawinsider.com/dictionary/media-content#:~:text=Copy-,Media%20Content%20means%20data%2C%20digital%20code%2C%20images%2C%20graphics%2C,the%20purpose%20of%20the%20communication&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;explanation&#34;&gt;Explanation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Content is any information or media, such as text, images, or videos, that is created and shared to inform, entertain, or engage an audience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;real-life-example&#34;&gt;Real-Life Example&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Example Description&lt;/strong&gt;: I mostly use YouTube because it’s a simple platform where any user can create content about whatever they want. It’s very broad and simple at the same time.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How It Illustrates the Concept&lt;/strong&gt;: The platform and algorithms of the website make it informative for all of its users.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Content over the years have had many different definitions, and today it’s more known as something people create for a social media platform. Anything that provides information that is visual to users is content.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content_Hotko_AJ</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_hotko_aj/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 17:47:53 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_hotko_aj/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Content as defined by Deane Barker, “Content is information produced through editorial process and ultimately intended for human consumption via publication.” Barker, D.( 2016). My definition of content if fairly simple, anything that humans consume that is created by humans. Some examples of content would be websites, movies, and even YouTube videos. A movie is an example of content because it was created by humans and intended for human consumption.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content_Myers_Albert</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_myers_albert/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 13:27:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_myers_albert/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-content&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;content&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Dash talks about the phrase user generated content and how the people who generated this conent did not like the way the phrase represented them. He also talks about how a lot of younger people today refer to themselves as content creators. (Richman, 2022)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In my own words I think content is any form of consumable visual element that someone makes for someone else to view.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;content-example&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Content Example&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Streaming is a great example of why people call themselves comntent creators. I have a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.twitch.tv/xirrelevxnt&#34;&gt;twitch channel&lt;/a&gt; where I produce content whenever I stream.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content_coleman_bryan</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_coleman_bryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 11:21:14 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_coleman_bryan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Content&lt;/strong&gt; is information produced through editorial process and ultimately intended for human consumption via publication. In my own words, content is information available for either retrieval or engagement intended for users and people.&#xA;One example of content that I consume regularly are golf youtube videos posted by Bryson DeChambeau. &lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/1Rc37QkkbGg?si=H0Ub7dX0r2hTp8z5&#34;&gt;Here is my link&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;This example illustrates the concept of content as I, the user, engage with the information, the video of Bryson golfing and giving tips as he plays, and by watching it I consume it, and the videos are edited before they are posted.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content_nguyen_nhi</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_nguyen_nhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 11:18:41 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_nguyen_nhi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-content&#34;&gt;What is Content?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The definition of this concept definition that I&amp;rsquo;ve chosen is &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Content is information produced through editorial process and ultimately intended for human consumption via publication.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Barker, D. (2016). Web Content Management. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In other words, the explanation of this concept is &lt;em&gt;Content is information or ideas shared in different formats like text, images, videos, or audio. It can be found on websites, social media, blogs, and more, and is created to inform, entertain, or engage an audience.&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content_chen_ricky</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_chen_ricky/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 11:17:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_chen_ricky/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;content-definiton&#34;&gt;Content Definiton&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;According to Deane Barker, &amp;ldquo;Content is information produced through editorial process and ultimately intended for human consumption via publication.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Barker, D.(2016). &lt;a href=&#34;https://deanebarker.net/books/squirrel/the-basics/&#34;&gt;Web Content Management&lt;/a&gt;. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In My Own Words&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To my understanding, content is something that takes time and money, made by human for human.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;content-example&#34;&gt;Content Example&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An exmaple of content is Online Courses. It is something that take money and time to create, made by humans for humans. I am currently taking real estate online courses, the content inside are pages of paragraphs, pictures, and there is a human speaking every word.&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learn.colibrirealestate.com/&#34;&gt;Colibri Real Estate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content_bryant_henry</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_bryant_henry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 11:09:04 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_bryant_henry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-content&#34;&gt;What is Content?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;According to Deane Barker in &lt;em&gt;Web Content Management&lt;/em&gt;, content can be defined as information that was &amp;ldquo;produced through editorial process and ultimately intended for human consumption&amp;rdquo; (Barker, 2016).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In other words, this means that content is something that an individual put effort into creating and that was designed and created for another individual to interact with in a meaningful way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;content-example&#34;&gt;Content Example&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An example of content that I consume would be a YouTube video. I watch YouTube every day and I&amp;rsquo;ve seen many different videos on the platform. For the purposes of this, I&amp;rsquo;ll use the videos from one of my favorite YouTube channels, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@veritasium&#34;&gt;Veritasium&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chen First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/chen-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 10:02:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/chen-first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;italian&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;bold text&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;del&gt;strike through&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.instagram.com/rickychenrc10/&#34;&gt;My Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;example blockquoate&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:1313/posts/BoxingGang.JPG&#34; alt=&#34;boxing squad&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;testign again&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Define content (Ahmad)</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_amjad_ahmad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:59:49 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_amjad_ahmad/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Definition: &amp;ldquo;Content is information produced through editorial process and ultimately intended for human consumption via publication.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Barker, D. (2016). Web Content Management. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From slide:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ICT 302: Content Management Systems&#xA;3 September 2024&#xA;Dr. Spencer Greenhalgh&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Something you consume, not like food, but like entertainment for example&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Animation: &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Animation&#34;&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Animation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a huge fan of animation (I wish I did an art / animation major instead) and animation could be considered an example as it goes through a lot of editorial processes like storyboarding for example, and&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Livingston First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/livingston-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:59:06 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/livingston-first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;test-header&#34;&gt;Test Header&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;italic text&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;&lt;del&gt;strikethrough&lt;/del&gt;&#xA;Test information &lt;em&gt;TEST&lt;/em&gt; test&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;click-herehttpswwwyoutubecom&#34;&gt;&amp;laquo;&amp;laquo;&amp;laquo;&amp;lt; HEAD&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/&#34;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[click here](&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;f7e33f0b2dff66b1e5a833aabeb3e83970faac45&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nguyen First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/nguyen-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:56:29 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/nguyen-first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is my first post&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is the second line&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;del&gt;This is another line&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://makewithhugo.com/&#34;&gt;my link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;example blockquote&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:1313/posts/nhi.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;my alt text&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;this-is-another-text&#34;&gt;This is another text&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coleman First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/coleman-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:55:18 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/coleman-first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am very excited for football to start.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think the &lt;strong&gt;chiefs&lt;/strong&gt; will win.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotko First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/hotko-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:54:42 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/hotko-first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;text&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;text&lt;/em&gt; &lt;del&gt;error&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;test&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;test no line skip&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;skip&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://makewithhugo.com/&#34;&gt;my link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class Blog #1</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_young_sim/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:52:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_young_sim/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Content is &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip; information produced through editorial process and ultimately intended for human consumption via publication.&amp;rdquo; Barker, D. (2016). Web Content Management. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media. To me, this means content that is produced by humans for human interaction.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some content I regularly consume are YouTube videos(youtube.com). This aligns with the definitions because the videos are content that has been created by a human, edited, and then made for human consumption.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harp First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/harp-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:52:18 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/harp-first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;water-is-good-for-people&#34;&gt;Water is good for people&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOG&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parsons First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/parsons-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:51:35 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/parsons-first-post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adhikari First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/adhikari-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:51:01 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/adhikari-first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Intro&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My name is Sayana Adhikari and I am a Junior maojoring in ICT at the &lt;em&gt;University of Kentucky&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[my link] (&lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/fBB4MaBybyg?si=kcz3ATvo-Ci1qzbK&#34;&gt;https://youtu.be/fBB4MaBybyg?si=kcz3ATvo-Ci1qzbK&lt;/a&gt;) is my favorite song at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myers First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/myers-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:50:37 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/myers-first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;testing&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Testing&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a brand new start&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lets see if this works.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;lets-gooooooooooo&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LETS GOOOOOOOOOOO&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also go check this out &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.twitch.tv/xirrelevxnt&#34;&gt;my link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bryant First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/bryant-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:49:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/bryant-first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;this-is-a-test-post&#34;&gt;This is a test post.&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is only a &lt;em&gt;test&lt;/em&gt; and nothing that I type here matters.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Markdown is pretty cool. It&amp;rsquo;s taking some getting used to, but it seems to be a little simpler to use than HTML.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Test test test &lt;strong&gt;12345&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a test of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/dQw4w9WgXcQ?si=48ck8bncUCTUHC9E&#34;&gt;link function&lt;/a&gt; using markdown editing. Pretty cool!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;del&gt;The quick brown fox jumped over the lazy dog.&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Test again&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hayes McCoy: Define Content</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_mccoy_hayes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 05:15:42 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_mccoy_hayes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Content is information produced through editorial process and ultimately intended&#xA;for human consumption via publication.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Barker, D. (2016). Web Content Management. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-content-to-me&#34;&gt;What is Content To Me?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Content is a term that can refer to a broad assortment of things&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This can include&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Text&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Visuals&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Audios&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Games&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lessons&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;And More!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For me content can be defined as a piece of information, entertainment, or&#xA;an experience that is created for the pupose to inform, entertain, or persuade,&#xA;and this is consumed in a format that is either digital or physical.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hayes McCoy: My First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/mccoy-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 09:26:42 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/mccoy-first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;test&#34;&gt;&lt;del&gt;Test&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://makewithhugo.com/markdown-basics/&#34;&gt;Test Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Test&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Test&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Test&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Test&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Test&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Test&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;table&gt;&#xA;  &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th style=&#34;text-align: left&#34;&gt;Test 1&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th style=&#34;text-align: left&#34;&gt;Test 2&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th style=&#34;text-align: left&#34;&gt;Test 3&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: left&#34;&gt;Test 1&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: left&#34;&gt;Test 2&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: left&#34;&gt;Test&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: left&#34;&gt;Test 3&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: left&#34;&gt;Test 4&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: left&#34;&gt;Test&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: left&#34;&gt;Test 5&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: left&#34;&gt;Test 6&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: left&#34;&gt;Test&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;input checked=&#34;&#34; disabled=&#34;&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34;&gt; Test 1&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&#34;&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34;&gt; Test 2&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;input checked=&#34;&#34; disabled=&#34;&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34;&gt; Test 3&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a Test footnote&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:1313/posts/test.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;my alt text test&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;test-1&#34;&gt;Test&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;test-2&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Test&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Test Test&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;footnotes&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnotes&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li id=&#34;fn:1&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Test footnote.&amp;#160;&lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_kirkpatrick_sam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_kirkpatrick_sam/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;title: &amp;ldquo;Understanding CMS&amp;rdquo;&#xA;author: &amp;ldquo;Sam Kirkpatrick&amp;rdquo;&#xA;tags: [&amp;ldquo;CMS&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;content&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Definition&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;A Content Management System (CMS) is software that allows users to create, manage, and modify website content without needing technical expertise (Smith, 2020).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Explanation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;A CMS helps you manage website content without writing code, simplifying the process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Example&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://techcrunch.com&#34;&gt;TechCrunch&lt;/a&gt; uses WordPress to manage its articles, showing how CMS platforms simplify content handling.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How the Example Illustrates the Concept&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;WordPress enables TechCrunch to manage content efficiently without manual coding.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implemetation_kirkpatrick_sam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implemetation_kirkpatrick_sam/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;title = &amp;ldquo;Implementing a Content Management Workflow with WordPress and Teams&amp;rdquo;&#xA;author = &amp;ldquo;Sam Kirkpatrick&amp;rdquo;&#xA;tags = [&amp;ldquo;content management&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;workflow&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;GMS project&amp;rdquo;]&#xA;categories = [&amp;ldquo;implementation proposal&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In our GMS class project, we will use WordPress, Teams, and other technologies to implement and enforce the content management workflow. These tools offer flexibility and structure to manage content creation, collaboration, and communication effectively.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;implementing-the-workflow&#34;&gt;Implementing the Workflow&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;wordpress&#34;&gt;WordPress:&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;WordPress will be the central hub for publishing and organizing content. Each team member will have designated roles (e.g., author, editor) to control access and ensure the integrity of content. The revision history feature allows us to track changes and maintain accountability.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_kirkpatrick_sam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_kirkpatrick_sam/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;title = &amp;ldquo;Understanding Content Management&amp;rdquo;&#xA;author = &amp;ldquo;Sam Kirkpatrick&amp;rdquo;&#xA;date = 2024-10-07&#xA;tags = [&amp;ldquo;Content Management&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Digital Media&amp;rdquo;]&#xA;categories = [&amp;ldquo;ICT302&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Blog Assignment&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;definition&#34;&gt;Definition&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Content management is the process of creating, publishing, and managing digital content efficiently. It encompasses the strategies and tools that organizations use to organize and distribute content across various platforms. According to John Smith (2020), &amp;ldquo;Content management is the systematic administration of the information lifecycle from creation to archiving.&amp;rdquo; John Smith wrote a book about understanding content management.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_kirkpatrick_sam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_kirkpatrick_sam/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;title = &amp;ldquo;Simple Content Management Workflow for GMS Project&amp;rdquo;&#xA;author = &amp;ldquo;Sam Kirkpatrick&amp;rdquo;&#xA;date = 2024-10-03&#xA;categories = [&amp;ldquo;workflow proposals&amp;rdquo;]&#xA;tags = [&amp;ldquo;GMS project&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;workflow&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To keep our GMS project on track, it&amp;rsquo;s important to have a simple workflow in place. In this proposal, I’ll outline the phases each task should go through before it’s considered complete, as well as suggest class roles that can help move tasks forward.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMS_Ilunga_Victoire</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_ilunga_victoire/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_ilunga_victoire/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;definition&#34;&gt;Definition&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content (Baker,2016).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;in-my-own-words&#34;&gt;In my own words&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In simpler terms, content management is the system behind organizing and managing information, like text, images, or videos, that you see on websites. Instead of manually coding or handling files, a &lt;strong&gt;Content Management System (CMS)&lt;/strong&gt; does the work of keeping everything organized and ready for use.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMS_Ilunga_Victoire</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_ilunga_victoire2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_ilunga_victoire2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;definition&#34;&gt;Definition&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content (Baker,2016).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;in-my-own-words&#34;&gt;In my own words&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In simpler terms, content management is the system behind organizing and managing information, like text, images, or videos, that you see on websites. Instead of manually coding or handling files, a &lt;strong&gt;Content Management System (CMS)&lt;/strong&gt; does the work of keeping everything organized and ready for use.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>workflow_donnelly_matthew</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_donnelly_matthew/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_donnelly_matthew/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;workflow&#34;&gt;Workflow&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;phases&#34;&gt;Phases&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Brainstorming - Think of ideas on what we actually need to change in the website&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Planning - Make a simple plan on how to execute these changes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Devolop - Devolop these changes on the backend&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Test - Test to make sure these changes are working properly&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Review - Review the changes and make sure there are no mistakes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Publish - Finally, we can publish our work after everything has been peer-reviewed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;roles&#34;&gt;Roles&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First I think that there should be different groups for different parts of the website.&#xA;Within these groups, there should be backend devolopers, editors, planners, and publishers&#xA;People that are comfortable with devoloping/coding could implement the changes on the website&#xA;Editors can make sure there are no mistakes&#xA;Planners can make a coherent plan so that it is easy to follow&#xA;I feel like everybody could be publishers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
