<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ICT 302 Fall 24</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ICT 302 Fall 24</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 04:11:58 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Implementation_lewis_grant</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_lewis_grant/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 04:11:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_lewis_grant/</guid>
      <description>WordPress will be our CMS, and we will use it to manage our content, from creating and managing posts and themes to ensuring the website is consistent and that information is updated. We will use teams to communicate and collaborate on our assigned parts and ensure others are doing their part. We also use teams to share files and task assignments. Using WordPress, we can see what people have done or changed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementation_Ilunga_victoire</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_ilunga_victoire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 01:38:14 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_ilunga_victoire/</guid>
      <description>Workflow description Once everyone has taken the survey and Once tasks are assigned, We’ll use Microsoft Teams as our communication hub where the groups members can report on their work and coordinate tasks. WordPress will serve as our main content management system to publish and organize the content we produce.&#xA;Workflow Expectations Follow the Schedule and Stick to the deadlines. Regularly check-ins with your Team and Dr.Greenhalgh. Communicate frequently and help each other troubleshoot issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow Implementation</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_livingston_chauncey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 23:08:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_livingston_chauncey/</guid>
      <description>How will it be done? We will have our multiple types of tasks separated into categories on Microsoft Teams, where the different groups can access them. Then, we can use those tasks to divide the work in WordPress. As far as the expectations of each person, it goes without saying that we expect everyone to do their role and, if they are struggling with their role, to ask for assistance. This can be done through teams or through our canvas shell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementation_adhikari_sayana</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_adhikari_sayana/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 22:50:51 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_adhikari_sayana/</guid>
      <description>Implementing our workflow&#xA;We will use WordPress, Teams, and other technologies to implement our workflow by assigning specific roles to class members and managing the content creation process. WordPress will serve as the platform where tasks like drafting, editing, and publishing content will take place. Each class member will have a designated role, such as editor, writer, or project manager, allowing us to streamline content production and ensure that responsibilities are clear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>implementation_Myers_Albert</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_myers_albert/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 22:50:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_myers_albert/</guid>
      <description>Workflow Description Teams will be used for task assignments that will be set by page. Said page can have their own &amp;ldquo;Bucket&amp;rdquo; that relates to the page. Wordpress will be used for draft pages and making sure that everything looks correct and is working before it is finalized. As well as figuring out what theme we as a class are going to use.&#xA;Expectations Teams: There tasks will be assigned, you are expected to complete your own tasks on time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>implementation_mason_avery</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_mason_avery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 21:27:39 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_mason_avery/</guid>
      <description>Mission Word press will be the actual working environment we will utilize. Here we will actually edit the project and implement our brainstormed, assigned tasks. MS Teams will be how we coordinate this project between groups. Propose ideas, assign work, strategize, and the main form of class communication.&#xA;Expectations Every team member will be responsible for their own share. Not one member should feel expected to do everything. Team members should be expected of contributing to the overall mission, regardless of their roles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementation_harp_mauricio</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_harp_mauricio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 19:45:44 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_harp_mauricio/</guid>
      <description>Use WordPress as a platform for publishing and managing content for the GMS class project. WordPress allows us to organize tasks and review posts for approval. Microsoft Teams will serve as communication. Teams will be used to assign tasks and report on progress. Team members can update each other on the status, flag issues, and feedback on drafts before final submission. Other technologies, like Google Docs, can be used to collaborate on drafts before moving content to WordPress for final publishing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hayes McCoy: Workflow Implementation</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_mccoy_hayes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 19:18:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_mccoy_hayes/</guid>
      <description>Implementing Workflows WordPress We will use WordPress for our content management&#xA;Allows us to keep an eye on revision history and check what has been done and what needs to be changed&#xA;You can leave comments on pages to provide feedback for these pages&#xA;There are so many plugins we can use to help implement a workflow, whether for collaboration, task management, automation, calandars, and more&#xA;Teams We can use Teams to communicate with each other and to collaborate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementation_Hotko_AJ</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_hotko_aj/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 13:30:44 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_hotko_aj/</guid>
      <description>Workflow Implementation The correct implementation of Wordpress and Teams will be very beneficial to our workflow. Teams will be used for gathering ideas and turning them into tasks. There could even be different chats for different roles and elements that need to be worked on so no information gets lost. Overall, teams is going to be more of an organizational and communication factor to ensure that nobody in confused on what they need to do.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementation_coleman_bryan</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_coleman_bryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 13:19:09 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_coleman_bryan/</guid>
      <description>We will use WordPress, Teams, and other technologies to implement our workflow by instilling a process of steps to help implement workflow. Primarily, WordPress can be used for content management as we can use this program to put each student in their chosen roles, such as an editor or project manager. We can then utilize Teams to help create communication lines between the various groups and roles as well as creating deadlines for when we need assignments completed by.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMS_bryant_henry</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_bryant_henry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 11:20:07 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_bryant_henry/</guid>
      <description>What is a Content Management System? In Web Content Management, author Deane Barker defines a content management system (CMS) as a &amp;ldquo;software system that automates the tasks around the management of content&amp;rdquo;. CMSs help content editors with &amp;ldquo;controlling, securing, and ultimately delivering content&amp;rdquo; (Barker, 2016).&#xA;In other words, this means that a content management system is a technology that allows a webmaster, website creator, or website administrator to create content and display it to users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMS_chen_ricky</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_chen_ricky/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 11:15:52 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_chen_ricky/</guid>
      <description>What is Content Management System? According to Deane Barker, &amp;ldquo;A software system which autmates the tasks around the management of content. A CMS assists editors in creating, organizing, controlling, securing, and ultimately delivering content.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Barker, D.(2016). Web Content Management Glossary O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media&#xA;To my Understanding Content management system is a platform that holds the content that people are publicly seeing. Its a easier way for people who dont know how to code to show their content on the web.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementation_chen_ricky</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_chen_ricky/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 10:55:11 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_chen_ricky/</guid>
      <description>How to utilize our tools First, everyone takes the roles survey and gets assigned a role they&amp;rsquo;re comfortable with&#xA;Second, with the tasks in the teams group, Dr. Greenhalgh assigns each member a task. OR every member go in the get a task they like and complete their task then move on to the next one&#xA;Third, after the task is complete, mark it complete, type a descrption or screenshot of the result and put it in Teams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>implementation_bryant_henry</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_bryant_henry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 10:54:55 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_bryant_henry/</guid>
      <description>Workflow Description First, we will post the required tasks to Microsoft Teams, moving them into the &amp;ldquo;Brainstorming&amp;rdquo; section on Teams first. Once the tasks have been brainstormed, they will be assigned to the relevant teams for drafting. Once the groups have drafted their work, the assigned project manager people will look it over and then show it to Dr. Greenhalgh for final feedback. If feedback is made, it will be fixed by the editors or designers before being finalized and actually implemented on the website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMS_nguyen_nhi</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_nguyen_nhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 10:53:07 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_nguyen_nhi/</guid>
      <description>Definition &amp;ldquo;A software system which automates the tasks around the management of content. A CMS assists editors in creating, organizing, controlling, securing, and ultimately delivering content.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Deane Barker, Web Content Management Glossary&#xA;In other words, a CMS lets you build and run a website without having to be a web developer.&#xA;Example A example of a CMS is my favorite recipe blog, Apple Pie by Grandma Ople. The person running the blog can add new recipes, edit old ones, and organize all the content in categories like “pie” or “cakes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>implementation_nguyen_nhi</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_nguyen_nhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 10:53:07 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_nguyen_nhi/</guid>
      <description>How to implement our workflow We will use WordPress and Teams to help our class stay organized and connected. WordPress will be where students can share their work and updates. We will post our updates about our progress and that will allow everyone to stay informed about what others are doing. We also use Teams to assign tasks so that everyone knows what they are responsible for.&#xA;Expectation Group members should check in with each other to share progress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>management_lewis_grant</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_lewis_grant/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 04:10:52 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_lewis_grant/</guid>
      <description>“A wide-ranging term that generally refers to defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content. - Deane Barker, Flying Squirrel Glossary&#xA;What is content management to me? From the quote above, CM is how content is organized and presented. This can be due to how the content is organized, stored, and delivered to a person. Beyond that, with content management, it could also mean who gets to see the content and who can&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow by Ben Parsons</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_parsons_ben/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 00:30:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_parsons_ben/</guid>
      <description>According to Deane Barker content management is, &amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;A wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content.&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Content managment to me means, the management of man made entertainment, information, etc that is meant to be consumed by humans.&#xA;An example of content management is a Wix template&#xA;This is a good example of content management because you are able to manage information and have it organized using a website template from Wix.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defining Content Management</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_livingston_chauncey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 22:56:46 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_livingston_chauncey/</guid>
      <description>What is it? Content Management is referred to as &amp;ldquo;A wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content.&amp;rdquo; Deane Barker, Flying Squirrel Glossary. In my opinion it just means that there is information that is being organized or controlled using an editorial method.&#xA;What does it look like? We see examples of content management every day, especially on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Management_donnelly_matthew</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_donnelly_matthew/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 22:43:29 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_donnelly_matthew/</guid>
      <description>What is content management? Deane Barker says that content management is the “practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content” (Barker 2016).&#xA;In my own words I would say that content management is a way to make viewing and navigating websites easier, for users and for the creators of that website as well. It is a way of organzing types of content on websites.&#xA;Example This is a photographer and youtuber that I watch all the time, he even has his own website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hayes McCoy: Define Content Management</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_mccoy_hayes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 20:13:26 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_mccoy_hayes/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;A wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Deane Barker, Flying Squirrel Glossary&#xA;What Is Content Management To Me? To me, content management is the way that content is planned, organized, structured, edited, and delivered. Content management, essentially, is just managing content.&#xA;What Is An Example Of This? An example that I thought of when thinking about content management was YouTube.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Managament</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_ahmad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 20:13:26 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_ahmad/</guid>
      <description>“A wide-randing term that generally refers to the practie of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content.”Barker, D.(2016). Flying Squirrel Glossary. O’Reilly Media Self-explanatory, how you handle content, like sorting, archiving, etc.&#xA;Take GameFAQs for example, where users posts are organized by things like categories, subforums, etc.&#xA;[hi] (https://gamefaqs.gamespot.com/)&#xA;They use content managament by letting users sorting posts (Ex. Views), pages, etc. and they let them manage their posts, like editing them</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Management_harp_mauricio</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_harp_mauricio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 19:08:19 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_harp_mauricio/</guid>
      <description>Definition: Content management is a wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content&amp;quot; (Barker, 2024)&#xA;Explanation in own words: Content management involves handling every step of the content lifecycle, from planning and creating to reviewing, organizing, and delivering it to the audience&#xA;Real-life example: I use YouTube, an example of content management. YouTube creators upload and manage their videos, organized through channels and search algorithms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Management_mason_avery</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_mason_avery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 16:55:51 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_mason_avery/</guid>
      <description>Definition &amp;lsquo;A wide-ranging term that generally rerfers to the practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing and delivering content&amp;rsquo;- Deane Barker&#xA;My own words Content management is the organization of content in regards to its particular users and specific practices.&#xA;Example Reddit is a content management system that allows users to contribute to what they call &amp;ldquo;communities&amp;rdquo; and organizes their posts to those specific threads. Links &amp;lsquo;hot&amp;rsquo; topics and recommends other communities to authors/users that may be interested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Management_adhikari_sayana</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_adhikari_sayana/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 15:30:37 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_adhikari_sayana/</guid>
      <description>What is content management?&#xA;&amp;ldquo;A wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating, oraganizing,securing,reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content.&amp;rdquo; (Deane Barker, Flying Squirrel Glossary)&#xA;In my own words&#xA;Content management is the process of handling digital content, from creating and editing to organizing and publishing it.&#xA;Example&#xA;Shopify is a widely known content management system specifically designed for e-commerce. It allows users to create and manage online stores, providing tools for product management, payment processing, and order fulfillment, making it easier for businesses to sell products online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Management_Hotko_AJ</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_hotko_aj/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 14:16:18 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_hotko_aj/</guid>
      <description>Content Management Defined “A wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content.” (The Web Content Management Glossary, Barker 2016).&#xA;My Take on Content Management Content Management is the way that we generally organize our content in a manner in which is the most logical and efficient.&#xA;Example of Content Management Google Docs would be an example of content management, you can create docs in which they are organized by date or name.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Management_Myers_Albert</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_myers_albert/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 12:30:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_myers_albert/</guid>
      <description>What is &amp;ldquo;Content Management&amp;rdquo; Content managemnt, according to Deane Barker is, &amp;ldquo;a wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Content Management in my own words To me I think content management is the content is organized for the consumer to see in a certain way. You could easily just put out unorganized content. However, people probably won&amp;rsquo;t want to view it, if there is no fluid motion of your content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Management_Ilunga_victoire</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_ilunga_victoire/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 11:59:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_ilunga_victoire/</guid>
      <description>Definition of content management content management A wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content (Barker, Flying Squirrel Glossary).&#xA;In simple words Content management is basically how we organize and handle digital content, like articles, videos, or images, to make sure it&amp;rsquo;s easy for people to find and use. It includes everything from creating and editing content, to storing and publishing it on platforms like websites or apps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Content Management?- Omari</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_chaplin_omari/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 10:26:39 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_chaplin_omari/</guid>
      <description>Content Management Our slides define &amp;ldquo;content management&amp;rdquo; as, &amp;ldquo;A wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content.&amp;rdquo; - Deane Barker&#xA;For me, I think of content managment as the thing that we or a team do to create, manage, manipulate, and organize the content we produce or otherwise have authority over. We make choices and decisions that we can make that will change how this content exists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>management_nguyen_nhi</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_nguyen_nhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 10:26:39 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_nguyen_nhi/</guid>
      <description>Content management Definition &amp;ldquo;A wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content. - Deane Barker, Flying Squirrel Glossary&#xA;In other words, &amp;ldquo;Content management is how we handle the information we share on websites and apps. It&amp;rsquo;s all about keeping everything in order so people can find what they need easily.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Example: A example of content management is Netflix. They add new movies and TV shows, organize them by genre, and update recommendations based on what users watch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow_harp_mauricio</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_harp_mauricio/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 22:33:35 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_harp_mauricio/</guid>
      <description>For our GMS class project, a content management workflow that follows several phases to ensure tasks are completed. First, the project manager assigns tasks based on the team&amp;rsquo;s needs. The content creator develops the content. Once completed, the content moves into the review phase, where another team member checks for accuracy and alignment with project goals. An editor refines the content, ensuring it is ready for submission. The final approvers does one last check before the content is published or submitted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>management_chen_ricky</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_chen_ricky/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 11:22:45 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_chen_ricky/</guid>
      <description>Content Management Definiton According to Deane Barker, &amp;ldquo;A wide-randing term that generally refers to the practie of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Barker, D.(2016). Flying Squirrel Glossary. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media&#xA;In My Own Words&#xA;To my understanding, content management is something a human do make sure what they&amp;rsquo;re publishing is understandable to other humans.&#xA;Content Management Example An exmaple of content is news articles. News article is something a human has to create, organize, review, approve, published, and finally deliver to the public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>management_bryant_henry</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_bryant_henry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 10:55:07 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_bryant_henry/</guid>
      <description>What is Content Management? In Flying Squirrel Glossary, author Deane Barker defines content management as a &amp;ldquo;wide-ranging&amp;rdquo; term that refers to the &amp;ldquo;practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content&amp;rdquo; (Barker, 2016).&#xA;In other words, this means that content management is the process of working with and processing the content that a user sees on a particular platform before the user gets to see the content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation_Ilunga_victoire</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_ilunga_victoire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:51:32 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_ilunga_victoire/</guid>
      <description>Definition &amp;quot; The general concept and processes around modifying content for display in a particular channel, usaually through templating. A template apllied will result in output which is then delivered.&amp;quot; -Deanne Barker, *web content management glossary&#xA;In my own words Presentation is how content is adapted and displayed depending on the platform. This is done by applying templates that determine the structure and layout of the content.&#xA;Example Canva. Canva is an online tool for graphic design that helps users create different types of visual content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation_Ilunga_victoire</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_ilunga_victoire2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:51:32 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_ilunga_victoire2/</guid>
      <description>Definition &amp;quot; The general concept and processes around modifying content for display in a particular channel, usaually through templating. A template apllied will result in output which is then delivered.&amp;quot; -Deanne Barker, *web content management glossary&#xA;In my own words Presentation is how content is adapted and displayed depending on the platform. This is done by applying templates that determine the structure and layout of the content.&#xA;Example Canva. Canva is an online tool for graphic design that helps users create different types of visual content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worflow_Ilunga_Victoire</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_ilunga_victoire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:51:32 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_ilunga_victoire/</guid>
      <description>Phases First, we will start by defining our project objectives so everyone understands what we want to accomplish. Then, we will break down the project into smaller tasks and assign them based on each person’s strengths. Then we should set deadlines to keep us on track and ensures timely completion. Once tasks are completed, we’ll compile drafts for review to get feddbacks from everyone.&#xA;Roles project manager content creators Editors Developers </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow Proposal</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_livingston_chauncey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 23:48:14 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_livingston_chauncey/</guid>
      <description>Task Phases I think there should be couple phases for the tasks starting with deciding what the task is and how indepth it will be. Next, we should decide which part of the website the task belongs to, is it part fo the main home page or is it part of an external link? Once that&amp;rsquo;s figured out that will determine who it goes to and they can begin to work on it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow_kapanga_rael</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_kapanga_rael/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 20:38:39 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_kapanga_rael/</guid>
      <description>content creation work flow:&#xA;Before starting to work on our class project, we should consider the following steps:&#xA;Brain storming: This is where content ideas are brainstormed, aligned with overall goals, and scheduled. Content Creation: this is where we start creating content after brainstorming our ideas. Review &amp;amp; Editing: after creating our content, we review the content for accuracy, grammar, and overall quality. Approval &amp;amp; Final Review: after we have edited and review the content, we will have stakeholders take a look at the content for a final review and approve the content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow_adhikari_sayana</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_adhikari_sayana/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 19:59:53 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_adhikari_sayana/</guid>
      <description>WORKFLOW PHASES:&#xA;Plannig Phase: In this phase,the task is clearly defined. The goals, deadlines, and required deliverables are identified. Roles are assigned to classmates, and expectations are set.&#xA;Creating Phase: In this phase we produce the content itself, whether it&amp;rsquo;s writing, designing visuals, or creating multimedia.&#xA;Reviewing Phase: After the content is created, it is passed to one or more reviewers for feedback. This phase ensures that the content is accurate, aligns with project goals, and meets quality standards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow_Hotko_AJ</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_hotko_aj/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 19:04:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_hotko_aj/</guid>
      <description>Workflow When considering the different phases that a task must pass through until it is completed, it would be best to determine when this task needs to be completed. A hard deadline is important because people need to know how to organize themselves in such a manner so that they will have the task completed on time. It would be best to consider even putting that deadline before it actually needs to be done just in case something is to go wrong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow by Ben Parsons</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_parsons_ben/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 15:13:06 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_parsons_ben/</guid>
      <description>Workflow Phases Task Assignment: Tasks are distributed to class members with clear objectives and deadlines. Content Creation: Assigned members develop content (writing, media, etc.). Review: Peer review for feedback on quality and accuracy. Revisions: Adjustments made based on feedback. Approval: Final content approval by the editor. Publication: Content is posted on the class blog. Roles Task Manager: Assigns tasks and ensures deadlines are met. Content Creators: Produce the assigned content. Reviewers: Review content for feedback.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow_lewis_grant</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_lewis_grant/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 14:06:03 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_lewis_grant/</guid>
      <description>When creating a workflow, the main focus is fixing an issue or problem or working towards a specific goal. By determining our goal first, we can build a fine-tuned system towards our goal.&#xA;Setting clear deadlines and determining the sequence of tasks is crucial. This ensures that each part of the project is completed on time. If one team or group falls behind, it could potentially disrupt the entire project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow_Myers_Albert</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_myers_albert/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 13:48:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_myers_albert/</guid>
      <description>Process to complete a task&#xA;First, figure out what the timeline on how long it will take to do said task. Second, figure out who needs to do what part and who is most effecient in said task. Third, Give everyojne their assignemnts and a deadline for said assignments to be done. Now of course some people might rely on one part of a task being done before they can start, so make sure you have the correct priority set up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMS_coleman_bryan</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_coleman_bryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 10:28:01 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/cms_coleman_bryan/</guid>
      <description>A content management system (CMS) is software that helps users create, manage, and modify content on a website without the need for technical knowledge. I got the definition from here. In my own words, a content management system is software that can help a user when it comes to creating and publishing any type of content. For my example, I think Wix serves as a great content management system as it helps a user create, manage, and publish content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Can We Effectively Manage Our Content? - Omari</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_chaplin_omari/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 10:26:39 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_chaplin_omari/</guid>
      <description>Content Management Proposal Well, its that part of the semester!&#xA;When thinking about the workflow for our blog, we&amp;rsquo;ll have to consider an approach that has as little friction as possible as we make decisions on how we complete tasks.&#xA;Task/Prompt Find out what our task is, based on instructions and vision for the blog.&#xA;Idea Formation and Brainstorming With a task/prompt in mind, we can begin to think about ideas of what we want to post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Management_coleman_bryan</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_coleman_bryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 10:16:53 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_coleman_bryan/</guid>
      <description>Content management is a wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content. I got this definition from the class slides. In my own words, content management is the collection, management, and publication of any form of information or content through a platform. For my example, I think WordPress serves as a great example of content management. I say this as WordPress allows users to create, edit, and manage their content, which directly lines up with the definition of content management.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>management_kapanga_rael</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_kapanga_rael/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 10:16:53 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_kapanga_rael/</guid>
      <description>content management definition is a wide-ranging term that generally refers to the practice of defining, creating, organizing, securing, reviewing, approving, publishing, and delivering content. (Deane barker) classes slides . In my own word, content management is all about organizing, storing, and sharing information and media (like text, images, and videos) in a way that makes it easy for people to access and use. This can involve using tools and software to create, edit, and publish content on websites or social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow_coleman_bryan</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_coleman_bryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 10:00:33 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_coleman_bryan/</guid>
      <description>When looking at the different phases a task should move through before it is complete, I believe it can primarily broken down as we can begin by defining the problem and the objectives along with it. Next, we should plan out the schedule and see if certain aspects need to be done by a certain deadline. Next, any minor background research that needs to be done before completing the task can occur, and then they will actually carry out the task and fix it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Project Proposal</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_mason_avery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:09:25 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_mason_avery/</guid>
      <description>Tasks phases Assuming we utilize Microsoft teams and with the introduction of the &amp;ldquo;Bucket-System&amp;rdquo; Dr. Greenhalgh showcased. I propose we split the tasks sections into 5-6 buckets. 1st Bucket - General idea, or initial thought of something 2nd Bucket - Planning stage 3rd Bucket - assignment stage (delegating task to who should be responsible) 4th Bucket - Finished state (task is finished and ready to be integrated) 5th Bucket - Revision stage (review work for potential errors) 6th Bucket - Completed tab (to track what has been fully developed and finished)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_amjad_ahmad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_amjad_ahmad/</guid>
      <description>Order 1, Determine goals&#xA;2, Make schedule and set tasks, like a roadmap&#xA;3, Check in every now and then&#xA;4, Rough draft state&#xA;5, Get input&#xA;6, Continue working&#xA;7, Work on final draft&#xA;8, Review&#xA;9, Finish&#xA;Some roles Owner, co-owner, leader, worker, and manager</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation_Kemper_Lea</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_kemper_lea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:32:09 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_kemper_lea/</guid>
      <description>Content presentation is how information (or content) is structured, displayed, and formatted for users in various mediums, such as websites, apps, or printed materials. Focusing on the visual aspects of the content delivery such as design, typography, organization, interactive elements, and media inclusion/placement. Basically how information is shown to you, whether on a website, in an app, or print. A good example of presentation in my everyday use is the dark mode feature on Instagram/Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_Kemper_Lea</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_kemper_lea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:29:55 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_kemper_lea/</guid>
      <description>Content aggregation is the organization of content from various sources (websites, blogs, and social media) onto a single platform. Allowing users to access a variety of information in one place. An example of content aggregation is Lex 18 my link our local news channel. They have many different articles that are linked on the first page. If you click on the headline it will reroute you to that article. In addition to written content, the page also includes videos, headline stories, and a link to watch the live news show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ugc_Kemper_Lea</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_kemper_lea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:22:56 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_kemper_lea/</guid>
      <description>User-generated content is images, videos, messages, or social media posts that are created and shared by human users. These messages are produced and shared by individuals rather than organizations or brands. An example of user-generated content is a review left on a brand by users, reflecting their genuine experiences, opinions, and feedback about said brand.my linkAll of these negative reviews are supposed to warn off other potential clients for this apartment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow_mccoy_hayes</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_mccoy_hayes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:06:28 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_mccoy_hayes/</guid>
      <description>Phases a Task Should Pass Through Before any piece of content gets published, it should be throughly gone over until it is determined complete. Below is an idea of my on how we could structure these phases:&#xA;Planning Phase We need to define our goals. We need to get input from our peers and client. We need to see what we have to work with, and overview what is already there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>workflow_chen_ricky</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_chen_ricky/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 12:16:55 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_chen_ricky/</guid>
      <description>Phases to Pass Through First, identify the problem/goal, know the what is the final goal of this task&#xA;Second, braindstorm ideas and assigning the right person for this specific task&#xA;Third, drafts should be made including the different ideas in he brainstorm&#xA;Fourth, an editor/publisher should review the final draft to make edits, suggestion, etc&#xA;Finally, post into the site after majorities&amp;rsquo;s approval&#xA;Roles Roles will be important to increase the effiency of the workflow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation_harp_mauricio</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_harp_mauricio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 11:07:09 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_harp_mauricio/</guid>
      <description>Definition - The general concept and processes around modifying content for display in a particular channel, usually through templating. A template applied to content will result in output which is then delivered&amp;quot; (Barker, 2024)&#xA;Explain in Your Own Word - Presentation refers to how information is formatted and displayed using templates&#xA;Example - [Netflix] (https://www.netflix.com) presents the same movies, shows in different ways depending on your device, such as a smartphone, TV, or web browser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentstion_kapanga_rael</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentstion_kapanga_rael/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:54:50 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentstion_kapanga_rael/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation_Hotko_AJ</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_hotko_aj/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:43:03 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_hotko_aj/</guid>
      <description>Presentation Defined “The general concept and processes around modifying content for displaying in a particular channel, usually through templating. A template applied to content will result in output which is then delivered.” (Barker, 2016).&#xA;My definition of Presentation I see presentation as the visual appearance of content and how it can be formatted in different ways.&#xA;Example of Presentation An example of presentation would be looking at how news articles on websites are presented.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>workflow_bryant_henry</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_bryant_henry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:42:55 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_bryant_henry/</guid>
      <description>Different Phases There are several different phases that a task should pass through before it is marked complete. First, the task should be brainstormed; we should actually think about what we want to work on with the site. The brainstorming step would also include assigning someone to work on the post. Next, once the task has been brainstormed, we need to actually draft the task - we need to fix the site in whatever way we brainstormed about.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation_lewis_grant</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_lewis_grant/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 04:10:52 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_lewis_grant/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Content is the raw data, while presentation is how it&amp;rsquo;s shown.&amp;rdquo; -Mauricio Harp. For me, the quote by Mauricio Harp best explains what a presentation is. I would also say it can be how information is represented, such as charts or visuals, as well as text, in an easy way to communicate an idea.&#xA;One instance for me is the news app on my phone. Of course, writers could post articles without formatting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation_parsons_ben</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_parsons_ben/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:46:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_parsons_ben/</guid>
      <description>According to Deane Barker Presentation is, &amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;The general concept and processes around modifying content for display in a particular channel, usually through templating. A template applied to content will result in output which is then delivered.&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo;&amp;quot;&#xA;To me, presentation is something where content is organized together to share information about something at once.&#xA;An example of presention is this link of a presentation I was apart of.&#xA;This is relevant to my definition because it is a way to share different types of information and content at the same time in a certain format.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation Avery M</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_mason_avery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:09:25 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_mason_avery/</guid>
      <description>Presentation &amp;ldquo;content is the raw data, while presentation is how it&amp;rsquo;s shown&amp;rdquo; Mauricio Harp&#xA;What is presentation to me in regards to content To myself, like Mauricio points out, presentation is the visuals of content. The way the content is portrayed and how its viewed. I think of it like taking a picture. For example, I could take a picture of my physical computer monitor using my cellphone but visually the image will be distorted and unclear compared to a screenshot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defining Presentation</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_livingston_chauncey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 22:25:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_livingston_chauncey/</guid>
      <description>What is Presentation and what does it look like? Usually associated with content, but the two of them work hand in hand. Content is the information that is being communicated, and presentation is how it is displayed. A recent example of this is found within Apple&amp;rsquo;s new ios 18 where users can now use a dark mode on their home screens. This new feature alters the look of your apps and home screen, but all of the data and information you are seeing is the same.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation_adhikari_sayana</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_adhikari_sayana/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 19:51:12 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_adhikari_sayana/</guid>
      <description>What is Presentation?&#xA;Presentation is the general concept and processes around modifying content for display in a particular channel, usually through templating. A template applied to content will result in output which is then delivered. (Deane Barker, Web Content Management glossary)&#xA;In my words&#xA;Presentation refers to how information is displayed or shown. It&amp;rsquo;s about the look of the content, such as the layout, fonts, colors, and style. It determines how users see and interact with the material, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t change the actual content itself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation_Myers_Albert</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_myers_albert/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 12:47:55 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_myers_albert/</guid>
      <description>What is &amp;ldquo;Presentation&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Content is the raw data, while presentation is how it&amp;rsquo;s shown&amp;rdquo; (Mauricio Harp).&#xA;Presentation in my own words Good preseentation can make the content you want to produce stand out among other version of similar content. It also needs to be aimed toward the consumer not just the people producing the content&#xA;Presentation in Canvas Canvas has a great presentation as it is aimed toward college students.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation - Omari</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_chaplin_omari/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_chaplin_omari/</guid>
      <description>Presentation is specificaly the the visual elements of a piece of content that are displayed on devices and other channels to provide a specific experience for the user, according to Barker.&#xA;To me, I find presentation to be the aspect that you want the user to actually see, and usually removing itself from the code and back end as much as possible&#xA;One example of presentation is on UK&amp;rsquo;s website. What we see here is the actual content of the page presented in a way that looks cohesive and visually appealing!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation (Ahmad)</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_amjad_ahmad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_amjad_ahmad/</guid>
      <description>“The general concept and processes around modifying content for display in a particular channel, usually through templating. A template applied to content will result in output which is then delivered.” (Barker, 2013).&#xA;You could say it&amp;rsquo;s the aesthetic of something, like how someone shows themselves to others by how they dress, theie maneruisms, etc.&#xA;KDE Themes&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;ll use Linux (KDE to be exact) as an example, as you&amp;rsquo;re given different themes and one of them can change the general look of the desktop which can affect things like spacing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation_mccoy_hayes</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_mccoy_hayes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 17:44:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_mccoy_hayes/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The general concept and processes around modifying content for display in a particular channel, usually through templating. A template applied to content will result in output which is then delivered.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Deane Barker, Web Content Management glossary&#xA;What is Presentation To Me? To me, presentation is how content is displayed. It is what you see when you go to a webpage or an application, and it is anything with a graphical user interface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>aggregation documentation</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/aggregation_documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 08:48:20 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/aggregation_documentation/</guid>
      <description>All code needs to be added to the front matter at the beginning of the post–that is, between the two sets of +++ before you get to the &amp;ldquo;main content&amp;rdquo; of the post.&#xA;author Add yourself as author to all of your posts with the following code:&#xA;author = &amp;quot;your name here&amp;quot;&#xA;Your name needs to be consistent across all posts for this to work properly!&#xA;categories We will use categories to sort posts by assignment type.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Content Aggregation&#34; - Omari</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_chaplin_omari/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 10:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_chaplin_omari/</guid>
      <description>What is &amp;ldquo;content aggregation&amp;rdquo;? According to the slides and Deane Barker, content aggregation is a purposeful grouping of content for the purposes of organization or presentation.&#xA;Personally, I would describe content aggregation as using specific classifying aspects of content, and using them to group similar things together.&#xA;An Example When I think of content aggregation, I think about Reddit! One of my favorite subreddits aggregates specific flairs, and each post that falls under it is organized under them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation_donnelly_matthew</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_donnelly_matthew/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 13:24:37 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_donnelly_matthew/</guid>
      <description>Defining Presentation Dean Barker gave a great definition of presentation, he said that presentation is, &amp;ldquo;The general concept and processes around modifying content for display in a particular channel, usually through templating. A template applied to content will result in output which is then delivered.&amp;rdquo; (Barker, 2013).&#xA;In my own words Presentation is how you view something in it&amp;rsquo;s simpliest form. It is how you see a website, and how easiliy or hard you can navigate through it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_Ilunga_Victoire</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_ilunga_victoire/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 11:01:18 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_ilunga_victoire/</guid>
      <description>Understanding Content Aggregation Definition of Content Aggregation Content aggregation refers to the process of collecting information or content from multiple sources and presenting it in a consolidated format for users to consume. According to Deane Barker&amp;rsquo;s book Web Content Management: systems, features, and best practices, &amp;ldquo;content aggregation involves gathering content from external or internal sources, organizing it, and displaying it in a coherent way that adds value for the user.&amp;rdquo; (Barker, 2016).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_Ilunga_Victoire 2</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_ilunga_victoire2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 11:01:18 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_ilunga_victoire2/</guid>
      <description>Understanding Content Aggregations Definition of Content Aggregation Content aggregation refers to the process of collecting information or content from multiple sources and presenting it in a consolidated format for users to consume. According to Deane Barker&amp;rsquo;s book Web Content Management: systems, features, and best practices, &amp;ldquo;content aggregation involves gathering content from external or internal sources, organizing it, and displaying it in a coherent way that adds value for the user.&amp;rdquo; (Barker, 2016).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ilunga Victoire Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ilunga-victoire-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 10:56:37 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ilunga-victoire-post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>presentation_bryant_henry</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_bryant_henry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 10:52:17 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_bryant_henry/</guid>
      <description>What is Presentation? In Examining the Separation Between Presentation and Content, author Deane Barker defines presentation as &amp;ldquo;the use of colors, fonts, etc.&amp;rdquo; on a website that changes the way the content looks (Barker, 2013).&#xA;In other words, this means that presentation is the way that the content looks when a user visits a website. The presentation can include the font that the content is set in, the size of the font, the color of the background, and many other general visual attributes of the website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation_chen_ricky</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_chen_ricky/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 10:51:28 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_chen_ricky/</guid>
      <description>What is Presentation? According to Deane Barker, &amp;ldquo;Content from its aesthetic surrounding, so the &amp;lsquo;presentation&amp;rsquo; is the use of colors, fonts, etc.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Barker, D.(2016). Presentation. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media&#xA;To my Understanding Presentation is how content is show. Regardless how presentation has changed, the content will still be the same.&#xA;Example An example of presentation is themes for Shopify. Here is an example -&amp;gt; Shopify Theme&#xA;This is example of presentation. Shopify is a platform that lets entrepreneur sell things online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>presentation_nguyen_nhi</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_nguyen_nhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 10:26:39 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_nguyen_nhi/</guid>
      <description>Presentation The definition of this concept is &amp;ldquo;Content from its aesthetic surroundings, so the &amp;lsquo;presentation&amp;rsquo; is the use of colors, fonts, etc.&amp;rdquo; (Barker, 2016)&#xA;In other words, the explanation for this concept is &amp;ldquo;The presentation refers to how content is visually framed and displayed but the content remains the same.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Example One example I use is Instagram’s dark mode. Instagram allows users to change between a light mode and a dark mode, where the background switches to black, and fonts and icons adjust to maintain visibility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_lewis_grant</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_lewis_grant/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 05:36:19 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_lewis_grant/</guid>
      <description>Content aggregation is &amp;ldquo;An intentional grouping of content for the purposes of organization or presentation&amp;rdquo; Deane Barker, Web Content Management glossary.&#xA;This means to me what tools or ways we can organize information, such as adding tags to files, dates, or names. A real-life case of this is when I use Lightroom for photography. Lightroom allows the user to organize their photos by metadata and other methods, such as keywords, ratings, titles that can be created, and folders to separate groups of folders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_mason_avery</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_mason_avery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 21:46:43 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_mason_avery/</guid>
      <description>What is Content Aggregation?&#xA;&amp;ldquo;An intentional grouping of content for the purposes of organization or presentation&amp;rdquo; Barker, D. (2016). Web Content Management. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media&#xA;I immediately think to myself that content aggregation is more like content presentation. It&amp;rsquo;s the presentation of what the content is, how its organized, what links to it? How is it portrayed to an audience. How does the user see the content?&#xA;The example I have for content aggregation would be something like an individuals youtube feed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_donnelly_matthew</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_donnelly_matthew/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 21:34:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_donnelly_matthew/</guid>
      <description>Defining &amp;ldquo;Content Aggregation&amp;rdquo; In Deane Barker&amp;rsquo;s words, content aggregation is, &amp;ldquo;An intentional grouping of content for the purposes of organization or presentation&amp;rdquo; (Barker).&#xA;In my own words&amp;hellip; I would say that it really just makes it easier to find specific things on websites, since it uses grouping and organization.&#xA;Examples? First thing that comes to mind is Reddit. Reddit&amp;rsquo;s home page is super simple and is easy to navigate for new users, Reddit Home Page .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defining Content Aggregation</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_livingston_chauncey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 21:16:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_livingston_chauncey/</guid>
      <description>What is Content Aggregation? To me, content aggregation is simple; it&amp;rsquo;s just the organization of content. Deane Barker -someone who knows a lot more than me- describes it as &amp;ldquo;An intentional grouping of content for organization or presentation.&amp;rdquo; A straightforward definition, but content aggregation can get somewhat complex.&#xA;How is it used? One of the more common examples of content aggregation is organizing things into categories or using tags. On platforms like Instagram, people can add hashtags that go with their posts to add them to other libraries of similar content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_Hotko_AJ</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_hotko_aj/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 21:07:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_hotko_aj/</guid>
      <description>Content Aggregation Defined “an intentional grouping of content for the purposes of organizations or presentation” (Barker, 2016).&#xA;My Interpretation of Content Aggregation My interpretation of content aggregation is that It organizes content in a logical manner in which it is easier to consume&#xA;Example of Content Aggregation - Instagram A user can easily see content from creators in that they are following simply just by scrolling. On the bottom the screen the user has the options to make a post of their own, search for specific content, access an area in which they can see content posted by anyone even if they are not following them, and view their own profile.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_harp_mauricio</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_harp_mauricio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 16:08:32 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_harp_mauricio/</guid>
      <description>Definition: Content aggregation intentionally groups content for organization or presentation&amp;quot; (Barker, 2024). Concept in Your Own Words: Content aggregation gathers and organizes different information into a single space. Real-Life Example - YouTube playlists let users group related videos.&#xA;How it shows Content Aggregation - It shows similar videos in one place and makes it easier for users to watch or search for them without searching for each video</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_Myers_Albert</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_myers_albert/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 12:13:27 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_myers_albert/</guid>
      <description>What is &amp;ldquo;Content aggregation&amp;rdquo; Content agreegation is, &amp;ldquo;An intentional grouping of content for the purposes of organization or presentation&amp;rdquo; (Deane Barker).&#xA;Content aggregation in my own words Makes it easier to find specific content on the sites UI.&#xA;Content aggregation on TikTok Tiktok for instance has a for you page (FYP) section and a following section. This gives the user the freedom to choose between fresh content from someone they don&amp;rsquo;t follow or to watch new relased content from someone they follow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Define content aggregation (Ahmad)</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_amjad_ahmad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 09:59:49 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_amjad_ahmad/</guid>
      <description>“An intentional grouping of content for the purposes of organization or presentation” Barker, D. (2016). Web Content Management. O’Reilly Media&#xA;Essentialy the execution of how you show content (Ex. Formatting)&#xA;Forums 1&#xA;A forum is usually formatted into main pages (Normally on the top) and when you click one, will show a list of sub forums / pages to make it easy to browse&#xA;Take GameFAQs for example&#xA;[hi] (https://gamefaqs.gamespot.com/)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_mccoy_hayes</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_mccoy_hayes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 17:44:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_mccoy_hayes/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;An intentional grouping of content for the purposes of organization or presentation&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Deane Barker, Web Content Management glossary&#xA;What is Content Aggregation To Me? Content aggregation is how content is organized or laid out so that it can be viewed and navigated by users.&#xA;Examples? An example that comes to mind for me is BuzzFeed.&#xA;Here is the link to their site: https://www.buzzfeed.com/!&#xA;I used to spend a decent amount of time scrolling through their site to find fun quizzes and articles, and how they categorize their website made it easy to find a lot of different content related to things I was looking for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presentation_coleman_bryan</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_coleman_bryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 10:05:25 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/presentation_coleman_bryan/</guid>
      <description>Presentation refers to the visual elements of a piece of content that are displayed on various medias and devices to provide a specific experience for the user. The source for my definition can be found here. In my own words, presentation refers to the various aspects designed to help display content to the user. This can be achieved through both visual and information elements. One example of this concept of presentation is a YouTube video by Bryson DeChambeau.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_adhikari_sayana</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_adhikari_sayana/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 19:36:25 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_adhikari_sayana/</guid>
      <description>What is &amp;lsquo;content aggregation&amp;rsquo;?&#xA;An intentional grouping of content for the purposes of organization or presentation. (Dean Barker, Web Content Management Glossary)&#xA;In my own words&#xA;Content aggregation means gathering information from different places and putting it all together in one spot. It helps people find everything they need, like news or articles, without going to many different websites.&#xA;Example&#xA;Example of content aggregation is YouTube. YouTube aggregates videos from countless creators and channels, allowing users to discover and watch a wide variety of content in one platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGC_Ilunga_victoire</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_ilunga_victoire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 23:09:07 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_ilunga_victoire/</guid>
      <description>Definition of User-Generated Content I would define User-generated content as content made by regular users or customers that is usually shared on social media or other platforms. According to the article &amp;ldquo;A Straightforward Approach to User Generated Content that Connects,&amp;rdquo; user content is is original, brand-specific content created by customers (at no cost to you) and published on social media or other channels (Oladipo, 2022).&#xA;Example: A popular platform where UGC thrives is Instagram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGC_Hotko_AJ</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_hotko_aj/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 15:39:43 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_hotko_aj/</guid>
      <description>User generated content defined by Deane Barker as “Content generated by non-editors, usually from the public side of the website.” (Barker, 2016). My understanding of this definition is that user generated content is anything that someone who is using a website or app as it is intended to be used. An example of this would be reviews that are left on a restaurant’s yelp page. People (non-editors) use the app to generate their content which is a review of the restaurant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGC_adhikari_sayana</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_adhikari_sayana/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 14:23:32 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_adhikari_sayana/</guid>
      <description>What is UGC?&#xA;User-generated content (UGC) is published information that an unpaid contributor provides to a website. The information might be a photo, video, blog or discussion forum post, poll response or comment made through a social media website (Kinza Yasar, 2022). UGC can include: Text,Photos,Videos,Audio,Reviews,Podcasts,Blog posts,Testimonials,Software, like video game mods.&#xA;In my own words&#xA;UGC stands for User-Generated Content. It includes photos, videos, post that are created by regular people post and not the companies on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content_adhikari_sayana</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_adhikari_sayana/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 14:03:34 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_adhikari_sayana/</guid>
      <description>Whai is Content?&#xA;Content is a type of information that is made to engage, inform, or entertain the audience. Content can be in various formats such as text, images, videos, audio and any type of interactive elements.&#xA;In my own words&#xA;In my opinion content is something that we consume through digital platform. Watching some content and consuming entertainment plus some valuable information is a plus point cause you are not wasting your time but doing something mindful.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>content_Ilunga_Victoire.md</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_ilunga_victoire_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 10:19:24 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_ilunga_victoire_post/</guid>
      <description>Defining Content Content refers to information or experiences meant to inform or engage an audience (author: Merriam Webster dictionnary).&#xA;In simpler terms, content is anything shared with others to communicate, be it a blog post, social media update, video, or podcast.&#xA;Example of Content One example of content I consume is Canvas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizing Content Grant</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_lewis_grant/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 15:23:23 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_lewis_grant/</guid>
      <description>##User Generated Content&#xA;In the past week, we have discussed user-generated content and its meaning. User-generated content or media created by a human. In the Podcast Episode: Wordle and the Web We Need a Podcast on EFF, the hosts talk about the meaning and what they feel by it. One of the hosts says it was crazy that people now refer to media or art, such as music, as content and sometimes not as its correct form, even when it comes from the heart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGC_harp_mauricio</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_harp_mauricio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 15:23:23 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_harp_mauricio/</guid>
      <description>Definition of UGC User-generated content refers to &amp;ldquo;content generated by non-editors, usually from the public side of the website&amp;rdquo; (Source: user-generated content and CMS extensions slide 14, Week 3). In my own words I think UGC is content made by everyday users, like posts and reviews shared on platforms. Real-life Example: Reddit Reddit is a prime example of UGC. Users submit posts, links, and discussions across different communities. For instance, in r/technology , users can share and discuss tech news, showing how the platform relies on user-generated content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content_harp_mauricio</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_harp_mauricio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:58:35 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_harp_mauricio/</guid>
      <description>Definition of Content: Content is information created through a report for humans to see through publication. It is organized and tailored to convey a message, provide entertainment, or share knowledge (Source: Slide 3, Week 2 Lecture, &amp;ldquo;slides on content, content, and mission, and content models&amp;rdquo;).&#xA;In My Own Words: I think content is any information that someone produces and refines to share with others. It’s engaging or informative, often reflecting the creator&amp;rsquo;s perspective.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>aggregation_bryant_henry</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_bryant_henry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:53:07 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_bryant_henry/</guid>
      <description>What is Content Aggregation? In Web Content Management, author Deane Barker defines content aggregation as &amp;ldquo;an intentional grouping of content for purposes of organization or presentation&amp;rdquo; (Barker, 2016).&#xA;In other words, this means that content aggregation is the way that content is displayed on a website in order for users to view said content via either the organization of the website or the terms that the user chooses to see. Content aggregation is simply the way that the content is displayed with other content on websites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_chen_ricky</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_chen_ricky/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:51:44 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_chen_ricky/</guid>
      <description>What is Content Aggregation? According to Deane Barker, &amp;ldquo;An intentional grouping of content for the purposes of organization or presentation.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Barker, D.(2016). Web Content Management. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media&#xA;To my Understanding Content Aggregation is a specific way to organize content to show to the public.&#xA;Example An example of content aggregation is news pages. Here is an example -&amp;gt; Google News&#xA;This is example of content aggregation. Currently the page is the same for evveryone, in the public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>aggregation_nguyen_nhi</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_nguyen_nhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:26:39 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_nguyen_nhi/</guid>
      <description>User-generated Content The definition of this concept is &amp;ldquo;An intentional grouping of content for purposes of organization or presentation.&amp;rdquo; (Barker, 2016)&#xA;Deane Barker, Web Content Management glossary&#xA;In other words, the explanation for this concept is &amp;ldquo;The content aggregation gathers content based on certain criteria, such as a topic or keyword, making it easier for users to discover relevant content without manually searching for it.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Example One example I use is Pintrest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is **User-Generated Content**? - Omari</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_chaplin_omari/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 04:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_chaplin_omari/</guid>
      <description>What is User-Generated Content? According to the slides and Deane Barker, user-generated content is content generated by non-editors, and usually from the public side of the website. An example of user-generated content would be a simple Instagram post of a selfie. The user generated and posted it with the intention for people to see.&#xA;An Example One example of user-generated content in action is another awesome video by Claire Saffitz.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGC_myers_albert</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_myers_albert/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 00:27:04 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_myers_albert/</guid>
      <description>What is &amp;ldquo;user-generated content&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;User-generated content (UGC) is published information that an unpaid contributor provides to a website&amp;rdquo; (Yasar, 2022). Somebody puts out photo or video into the public domain that anhyone can use.&#xA;Social media posts are great examples of UGC. One video can be circulated to potentially multiple different accounts that then give the original person credit for the use of their post. These posts can give someone a potential platform to use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGC_donnelly_matthew</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_donnelly_matthew/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 23:18:45 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_donnelly_matthew/</guid>
      <description>Defining &amp;ldquo;user generated content&amp;rdquo; User generated content is typically &amp;ldquo;generated by non-editors, usually from the public side of the website&amp;rdquo; (Barker). UCG is extremely broad, really anything that anybody posts/replies to can be considered for this; however, to me I would say that it is content created by users, for others to view.&#xA;Examples of UCG Reddit Post This is a simple example of UCG. Even though this post is about 10 years old, this user was asking questions on how to set up a darkroom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hayes McCoy: User-Generated Content</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_mccoy_hayes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 20:05:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_mccoy_hayes/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Content generated by non-editors, usually from the public side of the website.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Deane Barker, Web Content Management glossary&#xA;What is User-Generated Content to Me? To me, user-generated content is content that is published on a website by users of the website.&#xA;What is an Example of This? The first example that comes to my mind when I hear user-generated content is Wikipedia. Here is the link to their website: https://www.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGC_mason_avery</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_mason_avery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:36:09 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_mason_avery/</guid>
      <description>User generated content &amp;ldquo;Content generated by non-editors, usually from the public side of the website&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Barker, D. (n.d.). User-generated content. Deane Barker. https://deanebarker.net/tech/glossary/user-generated-content/&#xA;To me User generated content are things in which users of a particular platform post/create.&#xA;Sources of content I regularly consume are that of Twitter, Reddit and various internet forums. In these platforms users are creating posts and actively contributing to discussions and or creating content themselves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defining User-Generated Content</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_livingston_chauncey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:33:21 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_livingston_chauncey/</guid>
      <description>What Even Is User-Generated Content? When speaking about content on the Internet, it is almost impossible not to mention user-generated content. There are millions of new pieces of content on the internet every day, and they don&amp;rsquo;t just appear out of thin air, they are fueled&#x9;by people like me and you. UGC was referred to as &amp;ldquo;Content generated by non-editors, usually from the public side of the website&amp;rdquo; by Deane Barker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Define user generated content (Ahmad)</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_amjad_ahmad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 09:59:49 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_amjad_ahmad/</guid>
      <description>User-generated content (UGC) is published information that an unpaid contributor provides to a website. The information might be a photo, video, blog or discussion forum post, poll response or comment made through a social media website. (TechTarget)&#xA;Content by the general public and not those like corporations, moderators, etc.&#xA;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Internet_forum They&amp;rsquo;re message bpards&#xA;Forums are an example, where users make posts in sub forums while mods or admin make posts in the home page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregation_coleman_bryan</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_coleman_bryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 12:37:01 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/aggregation_coleman_bryan/</guid>
      <description>Content aggregation can be defined as the process of collecting and showcasing related content from a plethora of sources in one singular place. I got this definition from this website. In my own words, content aggregation is the topic of gathering and collecting content, information, or data for the user from outside sources and displaying it all together on a singular website or platform. A great example of this topic is Google News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGC_coleman_bryan</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_coleman_bryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 10:28:17 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_coleman_bryan/</guid>
      <description>User-generated content is content generated by non-editors, usually from the public side of the website. I got this definition from the class sides, which can be found here. In my own words, user-generated content is any published type of information or media where a contributor or user provides that information as opposed to an editor. One example I have for user-generated content is that I always read or look at customer reviews before I purchase anything online, such as from Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGC_nguyen_nhi</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_nguyen_nhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 10:26:39 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_nguyen_nhi/</guid>
      <description>User-generated Content The definition of this concept is &amp;ldquo;Content generated by non-editors, usually from the public side of the website.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Deane Barker, Web Content Management glossary&#xA;In other words, the explanation for this concept is &amp;ldquo;User-generated content are the contents that are created and shared by users. This can include social media posts, blog articles, product reviews, and more.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Example NikkieTutorials YouTube NikkieTutorials is a popular beauty YouTuber who creates and shares makeup tutorials, product reviews, and other beauty-related content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGC_bryant_henry</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_bryant_henry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 10:24:07 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_bryant_henry/</guid>
      <description>What is User-Generated Content? In Web Content Management, author Deane Barker defines user-generated content as content (see last post for definition) that was &amp;ldquo;generated by non-editors, usually from the public side of the website&amp;rdquo; (Barker, 2016).&#xA;In other words, this means that user-generated content is something that someone who visits or uses a website uploads to the website for other users to view and interact with, without going into the backend of the website to edit the raw code powering it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGC_chen_ricky</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_chen_ricky/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 10:23:27 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ugc_chen_ricky/</guid>
      <description>What is User-Generated Content? According to Deane Barker, &amp;ldquo;Content generated by non-editors, usually from the public side of the website.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Barker, D.(2016). Web Content Management. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media&#xA;To my Understanding User generated content is something that is created by non professionals and usually shows the real/raw identity of something without getting paid.&#xA;Example An example of user generated content is reviews for a Amazon product. Here is an example -&amp;gt; Amazon Review</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content definition by Ben</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_parsons_ben/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 10:16:12 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_parsons_ben/</guid>
      <description>According to Dr. Barker, &amp;ldquo;Content is information produced through editorial process and ultimately intended for human consumption via publication.&amp;rdquo; Barker, D. (2016). Web Content Management. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media.&#xA;For me, I believe that content is something that is meant to entertain other people, inform people, and or help people. It is also something that is created by humans for humans.&#xA;An example of a piece of content is a how to youtube video This ties to my definition because this video is a video that is made by a person for someone to learn something new.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content_kemper_lea</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_kemper_lea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 10:11:20 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_kemper_lea/</guid>
      <description>What is Content? Content is created in an editorial process and designed for human consumption. In the editorial process, content is often influenced by the creators&amp;rsquo; vision, voice, and guidelines of the platform or organization, in order to convey a certain message. I post content for the Tattoo parlor I work for. I use Instagram, Facebook, and our website to distribute pictures, videos, and announcements. To keep up to date with trends I regularly consume content from other tattoo artist posts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is **Content**? - Omari</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_chaplin_omari/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 04:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_chaplin_omari/</guid>
      <description>What is Content? According to the slides and Deane Barker, content is created by editorial process and intended for consumption by a human audience. To me, content is anything we humans create and put onto the internet. Anything from blogposts, to videos, to music, to images: all of it is content!&#xA;An Example One example of content in action is this awesome video by Claire Saffitz. In this video, she demonstrates one of her recipes from her book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaplin First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/chaplin-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 23:43:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/chaplin-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m Omari and this is my first post! My favorite website is Google!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content Livingston Chauncey</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_livingston_chauncey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 23:06:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_livingston_chauncey/</guid>
      <description>What is Content? Formally &amp;ldquo;Content is information produced through editorial process and ultimately intended for human consumption via publication.&amp;rdquo; Barker, D. (2016). Web Content Management. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media In my opinion content is various types of information or media shared on any type of platform. For example here is a website that has multiple types of content including an article and pictures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content Rael Kapanga</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content-rael-kapanga/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 20:08:06 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content-rael-kapanga/</guid>
      <description>definition: content is every type of information on the internet made uploaded by human for the purpose to be consume by human.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lastname First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/lastname-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 20:06:23 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/lastname-first-post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content_mason_avery</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_mason_avery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 16:26:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_mason_avery/</guid>
      <description>“Content is information produced through editorial process and ultimately intended for human consumption via publication.” Barker, D. (2016). Web Content Management. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media&#xA;I understand this concept as the creation of something with humans as the consumers. Videos, movies, podcasts, interviews, books and journals are some examples. Authors write books with the hopes that someone consumes them, i.e. reads their work. A chef creates a dish that he hopes customers will enjoy etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kapanga First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/kapanga-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 11:23:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/kapanga-first-post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kapanga Rael Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/kapanga-rael-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 11:22:35 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/kapanga-rael-post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>content_donnelly_matthew</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_donnelly_matthew/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 11:17:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_donnelly_matthew/</guid>
      <description>What is Content? &amp;ldquo;Definition of Content&amp;rdquo; Content would be something that users create and is &amp;ldquo;intended for consumption by a human audience&amp;rdquo; (Barker, 2016)&#xA;My Definition would be technically anything can be content; however, it needs to have that editorial process and needs to be consumed by humans in the simplest of terms.&#xA;Content that I regularly consume&#xA;If I ever feel like some of my photos are lacking any substance, I usually check out this website my link The reason that this website is content is that this is made for a human audiences, for creatives that are looking to find inspiration or try and recreate a visual shot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementation Proposal</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_donnelly_matthew/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 11:17:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_donnelly_matthew/</guid>
      <description>Workflow implementation The very first step that we should take is communicating on teams. Brainstorm on their and publish our ideas. Taking our brainstorm to the next step then implenting them into wordpress. After this, edits will be done to make sure that this process goes by smoothly. After everything is approved, we can finally ad the finishing touches then publish them to the website.&#xA;Class expectations I think that people should work on all roles; however, if people are not comfortable enough about working directly with wordpress, then they should focus on other tasks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow Implementation Proposition- Omari</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_chaplin_omari/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 11:17:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implementation_chaplin_omari/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s Make a Plan! We need to think about how our workflow will go&amp;hellip;&#xA;We have a few technologies available to us that we can use to implement and execute our workflow in WordPress, Teams, e-mail, Canvas, and any other technologies we bring into consideration.&#xA;We can use these tools to: Communicate with each other (text or voice) Set deadlines and due dates on calendars Share data and progress Screenshare Setup and attend group meetings Test and preview ideas Reasonable Expectations We should expect each other to use these technologies for the reasons listed above and more in order to get our work done efficiently.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content class blog</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_kirkpatrick_sam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_kirkpatrick_sam/</guid>
      <description>2&#xA;Definition Definition: Data, digital code, images, graphics, sounds, text or any other similar material regardless of the method or medium of communication of such content or the purpose of the communication. Source: https://www.lawinsider.com/dictionary/media-content#:~:text=Copy-,Media%20Content%20means%20data%2C%20digital%20code%2C%20images%2C%20graphics%2C,the%20purpose%20of%20the%20communication.&#xA;Explanation Content is any information or media, such as text, images, or videos, that is created and shared to inform, entertain, or engage an audience.&#xA;Real-Life Example Example Description: I mostly use YouTube because it’s a simple platform where any user can create content about whatever they want.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content_Hotko_AJ</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_hotko_aj/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 17:47:53 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_hotko_aj/</guid>
      <description>Content as defined by Deane Barker, “Content is information produced through editorial process and ultimately intended for human consumption via publication.” Barker, D.( 2016). My definition of content if fairly simple, anything that humans consume that is created by humans. Some examples of content would be websites, movies, and even YouTube videos. A movie is an example of content because it was created by humans and intended for human consumption.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content_Myers_Albert</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_myers_albert/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 13:27:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_myers_albert/</guid>
      <description>What is &amp;ldquo;content Dash talks about the phrase user generated content and how the people who generated this conent did not like the way the phrase represented them. He also talks about how a lot of younger people today refer to themselves as content creators. (Richman, 2022)&#xA;In my own words I think content is any form of consumable visual element that someone makes for someone else to view.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content_coleman_bryan</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_coleman_bryan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 11:21:14 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_coleman_bryan/</guid>
      <description>Content is information produced through editorial process and ultimately intended for human consumption via publication. In my own words, content is information available for either retrieval or engagement intended for users and people. One example of content that I consume regularly are golf youtube videos posted by Bryson DeChambeau. Here is my link This example illustrates the concept of content as I, the user, engage with the information, the video of Bryson golfing and giving tips as he plays, and by watching it I consume it, and the videos are edited before they are posted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content_nguyen_nhi</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_nguyen_nhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 11:18:41 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_nguyen_nhi/</guid>
      <description>What is Content? The definition of this concept definition that I&amp;rsquo;ve chosen is &amp;ldquo;Content is information produced through editorial process and ultimately intended for human consumption via publication.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Barker, D. (2016). Web Content Management. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media&#xA;In other words, the explanation of this concept is Content is information or ideas shared in different formats like text, images, videos, or audio. It can be found on websites, social media, blogs, and more, and is created to inform, entertain, or engage an audience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content_chen_ricky</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_chen_ricky/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 11:17:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_chen_ricky/</guid>
      <description>Content Definiton According to Deane Barker, &amp;ldquo;Content is information produced through editorial process and ultimately intended for human consumption via publication.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Barker, D.(2016). Web Content Management. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media&#xA;In My Own Words&#xA;To my understanding, content is something that takes time and money, made by human for human.&#xA;Content Example An exmaple of content is Online Courses. It is something that take money and time to create, made by humans for humans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content_bryant_henry</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_bryant_henry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 11:09:04 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_bryant_henry/</guid>
      <description>What is Content? According to Deane Barker in Web Content Management, content can be defined as information that was &amp;ldquo;produced through editorial process and ultimately intended for human consumption&amp;rdquo; (Barker, 2016).&#xA;In other words, this means that content is something that an individual put effort into creating and that was designed and created for another individual to interact with in a meaningful way.&#xA;Content Example An example of content that I consume would be a YouTube video.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chen First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/chen-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 10:02:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/chen-first-post/</guid>
      <description>italian&#xA;bold text&#xA;strike through&#xA;My Instagram&#xA;example blockquoate&#xA;testign again</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Define content (Ahmad)</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_amjad_ahmad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:59:49 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_amjad_ahmad/</guid>
      <description>Definition: &amp;ldquo;Content is information produced through editorial process and ultimately intended for human consumption via publication.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Barker, D. (2016). Web Content Management. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media&#xA;From slide:&#xA;ICT 302: Content Management Systems 3 September 2024 Dr. Spencer Greenhalgh&#xA;Something you consume, not like food, but like entertainment for example&#xA;Animation: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Animation&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m a huge fan of animation (I wish I did an art / animation major instead) and animation could be considered an example as it goes through a lot of editorial processes like storyboarding for example, and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Livingston First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/livingston-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:59:06 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/livingston-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Test Header italic text strikethrough Test information TEST test&#xA;&amp;laquo;&amp;laquo;&amp;laquo;&amp;lt; HEAD click here [click here](https://www.youtube.com&#xA;f7e33f0b2dff66b1e5a833aabeb3e83970faac45</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nguyen First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/nguyen-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:56:29 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/nguyen-first-post/</guid>
      <description>This is my first post&#xA;This is the second line&#xA;This is another line&#xA;my link&#xA;example blockquote&#xA;This is another text </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coleman First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/coleman-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:55:18 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/coleman-first-post/</guid>
      <description>I am very excited for football to start.&#xA;I think the chiefs will win.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotko First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/hotko-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:54:42 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/hotko-first-post/</guid>
      <description>text text error&#xA;test&#xA;test no line skip&#xA;skip&#xA;my link</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class Blog #1</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_young_sim/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:52:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_young_sim/</guid>
      <description>Content is &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip; information produced through editorial process and ultimately intended for human consumption via publication.&amp;rdquo; Barker, D. (2016). Web Content Management. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media. To me, this means content that is produced by humans for human interaction.&#xA;Some content I regularly consume are YouTube videos(youtube.com). This aligns with the definitions because the videos are content that has been created by a human, edited, and then made for human consumption.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harp First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/harp-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:52:18 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/harp-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Water is good for people DOG</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parsons First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/parsons-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:51:35 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/parsons-first-post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adhikari First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/adhikari-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:51:01 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/adhikari-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Intro&#xA;My name is Sayana Adhikari and I am a Junior maojoring in ICT at the University of Kentucky.&#xA;[my link] (https://youtu.be/fBB4MaBybyg?si=kcz3ATvo-Ci1qzbK) is my favorite song at the moment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myers First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/myers-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:50:37 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/myers-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Testing This is a brand new start&#xA;Lets see if this works.&#xA;LETS GOOOOOOOOOOO Also go check this out my link</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bryant First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/bryant-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:49:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/bryant-first-post/</guid>
      <description>This is a test post. This is only a test and nothing that I type here matters.&#xA;Markdown is pretty cool. It&amp;rsquo;s taking some getting used to, but it seems to be a little simpler to use than HTML.&#xA;Test test test 12345&#xA;This is a test of the link function using markdown editing. Pretty cool!&#xA;The quick brown fox jumped over the lazy dog.&#xA;Test again</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hayes McCoy: Define Content</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/content_mccoy_hayes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 05:15:42 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/content_mccoy_hayes/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Content is information produced through editorial process and ultimately intended for human consumption via publication.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Barker, D. (2016). Web Content Management. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media&#xA;What is Content To Me? Content is a term that can refer to a broad assortment of things&#xA;This can include&#xA;Text Visuals Audios Games Lessons And More! For me content can be defined as a piece of information, entertainment, or an experience that is created for the pupose to inform, entertain, or persuade, and this is consumed in a format that is either digital or physical.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hayes McCoy: My First Post</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/mccoy-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 09:26:42 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/mccoy-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Test Test Link&#xA;Test Test Test Test&#xA;Test&#xA;Test&#xA;Test 1 Test 2 Test 3 Test 1 Test 2 Test Test 3 Test 4 Test Test 5 Test 6 Test Test 1 Test 2 Test 3 This is a Test footnote1.&#xA;Test Test Test Test&#xA;Test footnote.&amp;#160;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/implemetation_kirkpatrick_sam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/implemetation_kirkpatrick_sam/</guid>
      <description>title = &amp;ldquo;Implementing a Content Management Workflow with WordPress and Teams&amp;rdquo; author = &amp;ldquo;Sam Kirkpatrick&amp;rdquo; tags = [&amp;ldquo;content management&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;workflow&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;GMS project&amp;rdquo;] categories = [&amp;ldquo;implementation proposal&amp;rdquo;]&#xA;Introduction In our GMS class project, we will use WordPress, Teams, and other technologies to implement and enforce the content management workflow. These tools offer flexibility and structure to manage content creation, collaboration, and communication effectively.&#xA;Implementing the Workflow WordPress: WordPress will be the central hub for publishing and organizing content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/management_kirkpatrick_sam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/management_kirkpatrick_sam/</guid>
      <description>title = &amp;ldquo;Understanding Content Management&amp;rdquo; author = &amp;ldquo;Sam Kirkpatrick&amp;rdquo; date = 2024-10-07 tags = [&amp;ldquo;Content Management&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Digital Media&amp;rdquo;] categories = [&amp;ldquo;ICT302&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Blog Assignment&amp;rdquo;]&#xA;Definition Content management is the process of creating, publishing, and managing digital content efficiently. It encompasses the strategies and tools that organizations use to organize and distribute content across various platforms. According to John Smith (2020), &amp;ldquo;Content management is the systematic administration of the information lifecycle from creation to archiving.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_kirkpatrick_sam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_kirkpatrick_sam/</guid>
      <description>title = &amp;ldquo;Simple Content Management Workflow for GMS Project&amp;rdquo; author = &amp;ldquo;Sam Kirkpatrick&amp;rdquo; date = 2024-10-03 categories = [&amp;ldquo;workflow proposals&amp;rdquo;] tags = [&amp;ldquo;GMS project&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;workflow&amp;rdquo;]&#xA;Introduction To keep our GMS project on track, it&amp;rsquo;s important to have a simple workflow in place. In this proposal, I’ll outline the phases each task should go through before it’s considered complete, as well as suggest class roles that can help move tasks forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>workflow_donnelly_matthew</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_donnelly_matthew/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workflow_donnelly_matthew/</guid>
      <description>Workflow Phases Brainstorming - Think of ideas on what we actually need to change in the website Planning - Make a simple plan on how to execute these changes Devolop - Devolop these changes on the backend Test - Test to make sure these changes are working properly Review - Review the changes and make sure there are no mistakes Publish - Finally, we can publish our work after everything has been peer-reviewed Roles First I think that there should be different groups for different parts of the website.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
